[Music]
[Música]
m
m
y
y
[Music]
[Música]
H Oh
H Oh
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
T
T
[Music] [
[Música]
Applause]
[Aplausos]
H
H
[Music]
[Música]
[Laughter]
[Risas]
H
H
[Music]
[Música]
Thank you very much Lauti for that huge
Muchísimas gracias lauti por ese pedazo
gift but today we are starting the live show
de regalo pero estrenamos hoy el directo
with 50
con 50
members 50 members crazy kid Hey
miembros 50 miembros chaval locura Oye
by
por
the way let's see how long I last today uh
cierto vamos a ver cuánto aguantó hoy eh
because this afternoon I went on telesalseo
que este mediodía me puse en telesalseo
And the truth is I haven't been able to be there as
Y la verdad es que no he podido estar
long as I would have liked because
todo el tiempo que quisiera porque al
I got stuck in nothing and the truth is I couldn't be there for
nada me atasqué y y la verdad no pude
long but oh well I hope that
estar mucho tiempo pero bueno Espero que
at least we have time to cover uh
por lo menos nos dé tiempo a tratar eh
most of the topics that you V
la mayoría de temas que te V aquí
prepared here how are you how are you
preparados qué tal
yesterday
estáis qué tal estáis ayer se me cayó de
Sara suddenly fell because yesterday of course in the end
repente Sara porque ayer claro al final
Since the status already failed me a
Como ya me falló un
little, let's say no, what I
poco el estado digamos no pues lo que
did was delete it directly and upload the
hice fue borrer directo y subir los
statements,
extractos
okay, by the way, wow, 60,70,000
vale que por cierto Vaya por 60 70.000
visits, not bad, not bad, yes, it's true
visitas not Bad not Bad sí que es verdad
that I was very sleepy, eh yesterday, chatting
que estaba muy dormido eh ayer Charlando
with Fran, the truth is that I
con con Fran la verdad es que me he
saw myself today and I saw myself very sleepy, I
visto hoy y me he visto muy dormido me
saw myself very sleepy, it's that I was in a state of
he visto muy dormido es que me coo de
surprise if he had told me and I had
sorpresa si me lo llega a decir y llego
known that he was coming, I would have
a saber que va a venir me hubiera
prepared some questions, honestly.
preparado algunas preguntillas la verdad
But anyway, I think it was good. I think it
Pero bueno creo que estuvo bien Creo que
was good. I saw that you all liked it
estuvo bien he visto que os ha gustado
a lot. So chill chill okay, over
un montón Así que chill chill vale por
there, the thing continues, over there, yuji
ahí por ahí sigue la cosa por ahí yuji
has put some others in
ha puesto alguna que otra en
directillo, he has finished understanding it
directillo la ha terminado de entender
very well, but well, we'll see how
muy bien pero bueno veremos a ver en qué
all this turns out and I hope it is in the
queda todo esto y espero que sea de la
best possible way, honestly,
mejor forma posible la verdad
eh, gibel talks about megamax,
eh gibel habla de
gibel talks about megamax, damn,
megamax gibel habla de megamax [__]
precisely the other day I sent a tweet
precisamente el otro día le puse un twet
to megamax, I don't know if he's going to be around here
a megamax no sé si va a estar por aquí
yet,
todavía
mm because I saw that he was breaking it, I saw
mm porque vi que lo estaba petando vi
that he was breaking it on Kick, hostias
que lo estaba petando en Kick hostias
Yanni Thank you very much queen
Yanni Muchísimas gracias reina
and what can I tell you, he had 7,000 or so
e qué te digo estaba con 7000 y pico de
viewers. Megamax, I don't know what he'll do.
espectadores El megamax no sé qué hará
I imagine he'll be doing
me imagino que estará haciendo lo del
anime, not reacting to anime, no, I've seen that
anime no lo de reaccionar animes no que
Uncle Shur look, here he is. I've
he visto que el tío shur mira aquí está
seen that Uncle Shur is also
que he visto que el tío shur también se
doing this. Now, it hasn't really
está dedicando esto ahora a mí no me ha
caught my attention, to be honest. But I
llamado mucho la atención la verdad Pero
do see that people are starting to get
si veo que que la gente se empieza a ser
rich here. Hey, let's watch
rica aquí Oye nos ponemos a ver
cartoons, I'll change and instead of
dibujitos animados me cambio y en vez de
Disney. Hey, we can watch Disney movies
Disney Oye podemos ver películas Disney
on Kick, in ki, we could watch a
en Kick en ki se podría ver maratón de
Disney movie marathon or not, megamas. How cringe-inducing
películas Disney o no megamas Qué cringe
when he imitated Rubius, man, but he was very, he was
cuando imitaba Rubius hombre pero era
very young, of course, let's see, of course, a
muy era muy chico claro a ver claro hace
long time ago. Look, I'm really happy for
mucho tiempo Mira yo me alegro mucho por
him because I don't remember if it was a
él porque hace no me acuerdo si fue un
year or two. Uh, well, he had this problem
año o dos Eh bueno tuvo el problema este
with Twitch, where they closed his
con Twitch que le cerraron el canal de
Twitch channel because of a problem he had with another
Twitch por un problema que tuvo con otra
previous account, okay, so to speak, some kind of thing and he was
cuenta anterior vale o sea una movida y
left without a Twitch channel while he was
se quedó sin sin canal de Twitch estando
just, uh, I don't know if he still lives in
justo eh yo no sé si sigue viviendo en
Japan, I understand that if I haven't  seen that he
Japón entiendo que sí no lo he visto que
returned to Spain but
se haya vuelto a España pero justo
just went to Japan to live that he was going
recién irse a Japón a vivir que se iba
to live for a year or two years or something like that
para vivir un año 2s años o algo de eso
eh they closed his Twitch channel dude he
eh le cierran el canal de Twitch tío
started like trying on YouTube or something I did
empezó como a probar en YouTube o tal yo
n't know he had gone to Kick
no sabía que se había ido para para Kick
but damn on kik if you have
pero ostia en kik si tienes
7100 viewers I have spoken with
7100 espectadores Yo he hablado con el
uncle sh about what he has been earning in
tío sh de lo que ha estado cobrando en
the discussions this Well I think he has
la tertulias esta Bueno creo que él lo
said it in public not in the discussions
ha dicho en público no en las tertulias
when he has had 3 4000 viewers
cuando ha tenido 3 4000 espectadores
for several hours and this is a lot of
durante varias horas y esto es mucha
money what meam is earning and I am
pasta lo que está cobrando meam y yo me
very happy because when they closed his
alegro mucho porque cuando le cerraron
channels there were people who were happy for
los canales hubo gente que se alegró por
him who were happy for him that he
él que se alegró por él de que lo
lost it eh who were happy that he
perdiera eh que se alegró de que lo
lost it So I am glad that
perdiera Así que yo me alegro que le
this is going well for him I think that nobody had their
vaya bien esto qué Yo creo que nadie se
heart broken when they told him that
le rompió el corazón cuando le digan que
Mr beast in fact falsifies videos
en efecto Mr beast falsifica videos
now here the point I think that many
ahora aquí el punto yo creo que mucha
people get confused is that I
gente se confunde es
say if they were fake they would  would take
que digo si fueran falsos se agraría
too much time in the hundreds of hours
demasiado tiempo en las cientos de horas
that he records for each of them Lu here
que graba por cada uno de ellos Lu aquí
Give some examples of Who in editing
Pon algunos ejemplos de Qui en edición
changed some things to improve
cambiaron algunas cosillas para mejorar
the rhythm or the continuation of the video in
el ritmo o la continuación del video en
Yes just like the Us cg like absolutely
Sí así como lo Us cg como absolutamente
any other competition show let's
cualquier otro show de competiciones a
see I'm going to tell you the truth and I think
ver yo les voy a decir la posta y creo
you know most of the things you
que ustedes lo saben la mayoría de cosas
see on the internet are false eh When
que ven en internet son falsas eh Cuando
someone does an extreme challenge it's not
alguien hace un reto extremo no es
extreme When someone does that it
extremo Cuando alguien hace eso siempre
was always like that both on TV and on the
fue así tanto en la tele como en el
internet gibel is a millionaire man I
internet gibel es millonario hombre Yo
think gibel earns a lot of money eh I
creo que gibel gana mucha pasta eh yo
think gibel earns a lot of money eh
creo que gibel gana mucha pasta
but I don't know how much the truth is I don't know
eh pero no sé cuánto la verdad no sé
how much eh Let's
cuánto eh
see it's not because he's
A ver es que es no porque él sea
Uruguayan per se but because I understand that because of
uruguayo en sí sino porque entiendo que
the schedule he has on
por por por el horario que tiene de
Stream man the cpm will be more or
Stream hombre pues el cpm será más o
less latan for sure no I don't know the truth eh
menos latan seguro no no sé la verdad eh
but I don't know I have no idea how much he can get
pero no lo sé no tengo ni idea de cuánto
paid Hey let's see if he
puede llegar a a cobrar Oye a ver si nos
tells us let's see if V this ex tro and he
lo dice a ver si V este ex tro y nos lo
tells us more than
dice más que
you Victor more than me anyone earns
tú Víctor más que yo cobra cualquiera
too I'm telling you eh  They
también te digo eh
also pay less taxes, that
también pagan menos impuestos eso
's also true, eh, I mean, what happens here in
también es verdad eh o sea lo de aquí de
Spain blows me away in half the
España a mí me sopla en la mitad de la
people who want to see it as
gente que lo quiere ver como
real, you're obviously fake, let's see, we
real tú eres falso obvio a ver esto lo
told this once with iox when we
contamos una vez con iox cuando
were doing a live iox
estábamos haciendo un directo iox
anduna, me or even da, we've talked about
yuna yo o incluso da hemos hablado de
anime that we haven't seen, well, I
animés que no hemos visto hemos Además
think that of course in Uruguay,
yo creo que es que claro en Uruguay
also it's true that he gets
además sí que es verdad que el si él
paid in dollars,
cobra en dólares
imagine, for example, I don't think I know,
imagínate Por ejemplo creo no lo sé
correct me if I'm wrong, but I think that I
corregidme si me equivoco pero creo que
think that,
creo
for example, if you live in Spain
que por ejemplo si si tú vives en España
and you get paid 10,000 bucks a month, it's not the
y cobras 10.000 pavos al mes no es lo
same as if you live in Uruguay and you get
mismo que si vives en en Uruguay y
paid 10,000 bucks a month, I mean, if in
cobras 10.000 pavos al mes o sea si en
Uruguay you get paid 100,000 bucks a month, you're
Uruguay cobras 100000 pavos al mes eres
the [ __ ] [ __ ], the [ __ ] elite, I
la [__] la [__] [__] la [__] élite
understand, okay, why don't you leave Andorra?
entiendo vale Por qué no te vas andorra
Well, because not even a kiss because I have
pues porque ya ni un beso porque tengo
my life made here in Spain and well, I get
mi vida aquí en España hecha y bueno
paid enough, the truth is, I get paid enough, it
cobro suficiente la verdad cobro
really makes me angry
suficiente me da mucha rabia la verdad
because I pay a lot in taxes, I mean,
porque pago muchísimo de impuesto o sea
I've calculated  which is almost half
yo he calculado que es casi la mitad
you know at the end of what you earn
sabes al final de lo que de lo que ganas
in the whole year you add up what you pay
en todo el año sumas lo que pagas en la
quarterly what you pay in the
trimestral lo que pagas en la
declaration plus what you pay in the
declaración más lo que pagas en la cuota
self-employed fee and agency and so on
autónomo y gestoría y demás la mitad
practically half Okay then it's a shame
prácticamente Vale entonces es una pena
because you say wow I'm fine but it
porque tú dices [__] estoy bien pero
's that I could be twice as good and I'm
es que podría estar el doble de bienb y
not even going to tell you twice as good because of
ya no te digo el doble de bien porque
course twice as good would be not paying
claro el doble de bien sería no pagar
anything No
nada No
but man what do I know I think paying
pero hombre yo que sé yo creo que pagar
20% would already be good no and being able to
un 20% ya estaría bien no y poder Podría
I could have a lot more money for I don't know
tener Yo mucho más dinero para yo que sé
imagine taking away a lot of things I
imagínate quitarme un montón de cosas yo
know a thousand things no Javi would you charge more
que sé mil cosas no Javi cobrarías más
if I put together the mini we said no this
si montase la mini hemos dicho no este
anime is the great Masterpiece it's
anime es la gran Obra maestra es
incredible and we didn't even see it
increíble y ni lo
[Music]
[Música]
but I think as long as it doesn't hit
vimos pero yo creo que mientras no da a
anyone directly with that you don't affect
alguien directamente con eso no afectas
anything I mean it would be bad for me to tell you
en nada o sea sería malo que yo te diga
eh smos pays Monster I've never seen it
eh smos paga Monster que yo nunca lo vi
and I've already seen it four times a verio is
y ya lo vi cuatro veces a verio lo está
paying it because he wants us all to see it
pagando porque quiere que lo veamos
together but you already know that I know
todos juntos pero ya sabe que yo me sé
everything that
todo lo que
happens gibel  he doesn't earn more than 1000 euros full
pasa gibel no gana más de 1000 eur full
latam I don't think so, not less than 1000 euros
latam No creo no menos de 1000 eur
man, no
hombre ni de
way, less than 1000 euros no way, man, no matter how
coña menos de 1000 eur ni de coña hombre
full, no matter how full it is,
por muy full por mu full lata que
eh, I think this channel is his, I don't
sea eh yo creo que este canal es suyo
know, a million
no no sé un millón
[Music]
[Música]
put it to watch I don't know what to say, I don't know what to
ponle a ver no sé decir no sé qué
tell you, the truth, I don't know what to tell you,
deciros la verdad no sé qué deciros
but I think I do
pero creo
n't know, the truth, I think five out
que no sé la verdad creo que cinco por
there, yes, it will be between all of them 5-6000 pavet, I think it will be
ahí si sará entre todos 5 6000 pavet
between all of them, but I don't
creo que sí sará entre todos pero no lo
know, report times but also
sé report tiempos sino también de
places and why do you complain about megamax
lugares y por qué te quejas de megamax
because he says no because he says he did
porque él dice que no porque él dice que
n't watch series so they pay him
no vio series para que se las paguen
when he did watch them That's the only complaint
cuando si las vio Esa es la única queja
How much difference and the difference is
Cuánta diferencia y la diferencia es
big, to make a video I don't ask you for
grande yo para hacer un video no te pido
money to watch an anime that I've already seen, I
dinero para ver un anime que ya vi te
tell you no, if I ask you for money, I think there
digo que no si te pido dinero creo que
's a substantial difference now
hay una diferencia sustancial ahora
What's up with that anime, I don't see that it has
Qué onda con ese anime no veo que tenga
much influence when talking about
mucha influencia cuando se habla de
sports anime, I think that in Spain
animes de deportes creo que en España es
inasuma Eleven is popular  what anime have you
popular inasuma Eleven de qué anime has
talked about without having
hablado sin haber
seen gel earns 10,000 to 20,000 the
visto gel gana de 10000 a 20000 la
amount they donate to watch a
cantidad que le donan para ver anime un
lot of anime and on top of that through PayPal so they don't
montón y encima por PayPal así no le
withhold
retienen
anything from 10 to 200,000 would seem
nada de 10 a 200000 me parecería
too much but I don't rule it out it
demasiado pero no lo descarto
's not too complicated to know someone
tampoco es mu complicado saber a alguien
because you don't know the members you
porque tú no sabes los miembros que
have the subscriptions the donations
tienes las suscripciones las donaciones
no you can't know I think
no no lo puedes
the first video I made
saber creo que el primer video que hice
of Tokyo revenger I did without having
de Tokyo revenger lo hice sin habérmelo
finished it, it aged well And the truth is I
terminado envejeció bien Y la verdad le
hit
pegué a
everything everything I criticized I hit one
todo todo lo que critiqué le pegué una
thing that I say I
cosa que yo digo
understand gibel have you ever
entiendo gibel vos alguna vez te
found out about some private gossip about
enteraste de algún chisme privado de
a youtuber streamer that if it
algún youtuber streamer que te si
came to light it would be a meeting of several,
saliera a la luz sería reuno varios
many several, what they said after
mucho varios lo que contaban después de
the evening and all that at the party of the
la velada y todo eso en la fiesta de la
evening and everything, friend, the things that I have
velada y todo amigo las cosas que me he
found out about
enterado de
people but I will never burn
gente pero yo nunca voy a quemar a
anyone, I
nadie yo
musarella to CP And if more than one eats
musarella a CP Y si más de uno se come
a pebete
un pebete
That is, of both sexes, not only, not only
Eso sí de ambos sexos no solo no solo
men with  [ __ ] but also
hombres con pendejas sino también
women with [ __ ] no I'm not going to No not
mujeres con [__] no no lo voy a No ni
even
por más
if Javi Juan threw a direct ind at you
que Javi Juan te tiró una ind directa
Well for me in his live the day before
Bueno para mí en su directo de antes de
yesterday I don't believe it Sari tell me but come on I
ayer no lo creo Sari dímela pero vamos
doubt it
lo dudo
very much 15 million bit first because
mucho 15 millones bit primero porque no
I wouldn't like to ruin anyone's life and
me gustaría arruinarle la vida a nadie y
second because I'm not interested in dissing
segundo porque a mí no me interesa funar
someone I
a alguien no soy tan basura Como para
'm not that garbage As to have to diss someone your character starts with c Ah no don't say stupid don't start And if I insult you strongly I don't need to attack with something personal I don't need to and he regrets it don't laugh what do I know I think that deep down when you screw up
que en el fondo cuando te mandas una
you regret it let's see but you're not going to
[__] te arrepentís a ver pero tampoco
make your life revolve around
vas a hacer que tu vida gire en torno a
what you did wrong in the
lo que hiciste mal el
past I found out that there's a
pasado yo me enteré de que hay un
streamer named Juan who went to the
streamer llamado Juan que fue a la
party And he had a controversy because his
velada Y tuvo una polémica porque su
girlfriend Was on Stream and when he got up he
novia Estaba en Stream y al levantarse
had a little carelessness
tuvo un pequeño descuido
what what did I say I also think that you guys
qué qué decí Igual yo creo que ustedes
If you knew that you wouldn't
Si supieran eso tampoco lo tampoco lo
say it either Or maybe you are really that [ __ ]  what would
dirían O tal vez sí son tan soretes que
you say,
lo dirían ustedes
the world of anime and all that
curioso el mundo ese de los animes y las
stuff is curious, man, I mean, the
movidas esas eh tío o sea curioso el
world of anime is curious and watching anime and
mundo de los animes y de ver animes y de
people paying to see it so
que la gente pague para ver Para que
you can react to anime, man,
pongas a para que reacciones anime tío
what's that thing, man, what's that thing, man, what's that thing, people
qué movida esa eh qué movida eh la gente
paying for you to watch anime But why, I do
pagando Para que veas anime Pero por qué
n't know, I don't really get it, it's that
no sé no termino de pillarle el rollo a
I like
mí es que me gusta el
gossip, David, I don't have time to
chisme eh David a mí no me da tiempo a
start any
a iniciar
other type of content, in
otro otro tipo de contenido más ya de
fact, these last few weeks I've
hecho Tengo estas últimas semanas
pretty much abandoned telesalseo, man, I
bastante abandonado el telesalseo tío le
have to give telesalseo a go and
tengo que dar caña a telesalseo y
revive it just like we revived the
revivirlo igual que revivimos el canal
main channel, which by the way, the last video on the Main Channel,
principal que por cierto el último vídeo
man, was really bad,
del Canal principal tío pinchó mucho
eh, it
eh No
wasn't much of a success, eh, the last
fue no fue mucho acierto eh el último
video on the Main Channel had 10,000 views,
vídeo del Canal principal 10.000 visitas
man, I mean, I don't understand why it was bad,
tío O sea no entiendo por qué pinchó
honestly, I think it's a very
la verdad me parece un tema muy
cool topic. Well, do you get paid for gossip, it's a
Guay Bueno a ti te pagan por chisme es
matter of taste? Yes, but well, it's different. I
cosa de gusto Sí pero bueno es diferente
don't know, honestly, because
No lo sé la verdad porque un anime para
why do you want a youtuber to put up an anime?  if
qué quieres que lo ponga un youtuber si
you can see it no I mean it's different
tú lo puedes ver no o sea es diferente
no well eh Ricky has spoken about
no bueno eh Ricky ha vuelto a hablar de
Dallas again in a very I don't know if I'm
Dallas así de forma como muy no sé si se
missing something these days that he's a
me escapa algo en estos días que está un
little distracted But it was gratuitous or or it
poco distraído Pero ha sido gratuito o o
came from
venía por
something or else what Ricky said came from something or it's that I did
algo o sea lo de Ricky venía por algo o
n't understand very well why
es que no he entendido muy bien que
Ricky suddenly came out with this in a
Ricky salga de repente con esto en
tremendous tweet with so much text the
tremendo tweet con tantísimo texto la
tremendous truth Bible went crazy I just did
verdad tremenda Biblia se mandó el ruk
n't understand it the truth I don't
es que no lo he entendido la verdad no
know if dasas must have said something
sé si dasas habrá dicho algo en algún
somewhere I know that today he did say Dallas
sitio sé que hoy sí ha dicho Dallas
after Ricky posted this but
después de que Ricky ponga esto pero
before I
antes
mean this thing about Ricky suddenly it was
o sea esto de Ricky de repente ha sido
because Dallas had done something had
porque Dallas había hecho algo había
said something or
dicho algo o
what are we going to read it I woke up
qué vamos a leerlo me he levantado
curious and I informed myself about how
curioso y me he informado sobre cómo
Dallas wants to manage this season of
quiere gestionar Dallas esta temporada
course here I say Well whatever
claro aquí digo yo Bueno qué
season it is how Dallas wants to manage
temporada sea cómo quiere gestionar
the the season this season but about
Dallas la la temporada esta pero sobre
what I mean I don't understand
qué O sea no entiendo
much I understand a lot About what I mean how
mucho Endo mucho Sobre qué O sea cómo
Dallas wants to manage this season
quiere gestionar Dallas esta temporada
what season since he hasn't given me any
qué temporada ya que lleva sin darme
signals since March but he has time
señales desde marzo pero tiene tiempo
to dodge bitcoin insults on
para sortear bitcoin insultar por
Twitter and warn that he will soon
Twitter y avisar de que pronto
respond to all the  that we talk about
responderá a todos los que hablamos de
him Although it seems like the day will never
él Aunque parece que el día no vaya a
come I mean I imagine Ricky
llegar nunca o sea yo me imagino a Ricky
super impatient every day
como super impaciente todos los días
watching the Dallas channel to see if
mirando el canal de Dallas a ver si
Dallas makes a video
Dallas le hace un vídeo
let's see I don't really think that Dallas is
ya a ver yo no creo realmente que Dallas
going to go when Dallas refers to
vaya a ir cuando Dallas se refiere a
answering people who say
contestarle a la gente que que le dicen
things to him I don't think Ricky is going to go on that
cosas no creo que Ricky vaya en ese
corn yeah what about Ander now we'll see I don't
elote sí lo de ander ahora lo veremos No
think it's that I don't think Ricky is
creo que es que no creo que que Ricky
going to go on that corn I mean what are you going to
vaya en ese elote O sea qué le vas a
answer Ricky this nonsense that
responder a Ricky estas tonterías que
Twitter puts and the
ponen Twitter y los comentarios de
shitty comments that are already more than peeled and
[__] que ya están más que pelados y
peeled I think he's referring more to these
mondados yo creo que se refiere más a la
people of his
gente esta de su
eh And I think that not even that eh the
eh Y creo que ya ni eso siquiera eh la
truth is I doubt I don't even doubt that it
verdad es que dudo ni siquiera dudo que
's doubtful Until Dallas is going to
sea dudo Hasta que el Dallas se vaya a
start being a delox video again
poner a ser un vídeo del delox otra vez
It doesn't make sense or even
Es que no tiene sentido ni siquiera
clear let's see when D posted that tweet I
claro a ver yo cuando D puso ese twit yo
understood that he was going for the ex mother-in-law
entendía que iba por por la ex la suegra
ex-mother-in-law and all these people no but
ex suegra y toda esta gente no pero
of course the days have passed I think
claro ya se han pasado los días yo creo
that  it's cooled down
que ya se ha enfriado
I think it refers to
eso yo creo que se refiere a
another type
de otro tipo
Eh yes yes I know he gives the answers
Eh sí sí ya sé que da las contestas este
we'll see this message now but come on
mensaje lo vamos a ver ahora pero vamos
I imagine Ricky as super
me imagino al Ricky como super
impatient no let's go Dallas make a video
impaciente no ay que Dalas haga un vídeo
please let Dallas make a video he
por favor que Dalas haga un vídeo se lo
took it personally ricus man it's not that
tomó personal el ricus hombre no es que
they have already entered into a takedown in
ellos han entrado ya en una derribada en
which Ricky's gossip
el que el salseo de Ricky pues
involved Ricky's personal issues and
involucraba temas personales de Ricky y
Ricky has gotten into Dallas' personal issue
Ricky se ha metido en tema personal de
to the max apart from me with Ricky who I have
Dallas a tope aparte yo con Ricky que he
spoken with him on many occasions and such
hablado en muchas ocasiones con él y tal
and he has asked me about things I have
y me ha preguntado sobre cosas yo he
seen that Ricky has lied about some
visto que Ricky ha mentido en algunas
things wanting to lie because he has felt like
cosas queriendo mentir porque le ha
throwing [ __ ] even though they have
salido de la [__] a tirar [__] aunque
explained the truth to him you know I don't know
le hayan explicado la verdad sabes No sé
I think that this In part well it's because it
yo creo que esto En parte pues es porque
moves I mean in the end hate to Dallas
mueve O sea al final hate a a Dallas
moves and there are people who don't that don't get out of
mueve y hay gente que no que no sale de
there no eh
ahí no eh
Look
Hay mira
yesterday I put a couple of examples
ayer puse yo un par de ejemplos
okay well This was great eh I mean it turns out
vale bueno Esto fue buenísimo eh o sea
that cti put a tweet and how
resulta ser que cti puso un tweet e como
they are taking out like a Dallas clip of de
están sacando como clip de Dallas de de
direct from him with miad to say that
directos de él con miad para decir que
Dallas abused her and so on again
Dallas la maltrataba y demás otra vez
going back to 2017 which is like man there are
volviendo al 2017 que es como tío hay
millions of videos about things and
millones de vídeos sobre cosas y y
millions of videos But well it's like a
millones de vídeos Pero bueno es como un
loop it's not like the people who don't know
bucle no es como el pueblo que no conoce
their history are doomed to repeat it
su historia está condenado a repetirla
no But well ciny took out a tweet with
no Pero bueno ciny sacó un tweet con
another clip in which well dala put her
otro clip en el que pues dala ponía su
partner at that time on an altar How
pareja en aquel entonces en un altar Qué
beautiful you are You are the best you give me everything
guapa eres Eres la mejor me lo das todo
blah blah blah blah bl Bla okay And then it turns
bla bla bla bla bl Bla vale Y entonces
out that cinty says like this is it gives the
resulta que cinty pone así es da la
review the hater community we reject
review la comunidad de hater rechazamos
these behaviors more clip of him and
estos comportamientos más clip de él y
of and his ex from the same Live that have gone
de y su ex del mismo Live que han
viral and that they have not taken out of
viralizado y que para nada han sacado de
context at all by conveniently cutting the clips
contexto cortando los clips
you can see how uncomfortable she is and
se puede ver lo incómoda que ella está y
how badly he treats her and the cocu the little
lo mal que él la trata y el cocu la
creature has given him a
criaturita le ha dado
like the little creature of has given him a like
like la criaturita del le ha dado like
uncle
tío
eh he has given him a like I mean he won't even have
eh le ha dado like o sea ni habrá
understood what he read if he
entendido lo que ha leído si es que le
has understood him I read it no and someone comes here
ha entendido La leí no y viene aquí
and says wow wow 9000  wow wow of
alguien y dice guau guau 9000 guau
course me when when when
guau claro yo cuando cuando cuando
When I see this of course I
Cuando veo esto claro yo esto lo
understand this we've already talked about it a lot
entiendo ya lo hemos hablado un montón
of times I mean this This can't be
de veces o sea esto Esto no te lo puede
written by a 13 or 12 year old
escribir ni un niño de 13 ni de 12 años
This is for 8 years old or
Esto va para 8 añitos o
seven 7 8 9 years old okay wow wow 9000
siete 7 8 9 añitos vale guau guau 9000
wow wow and I go into the profile to
guau guau y me meto en el perfil para
take a look at the
echar un vistazo de la
creature Oh why doesn't it sound Gerardo
criatura Ay por qu no suena Gerardo
wait
espérate
and I find out that it's a guy who
y me encuentro con que es un tío que
posts that he smokes joints and I mean he's a
publica que fuma porros y o sea es un
big guy eh He's not a little guy and
tío grande eh No es un tío pequeño y
he brags that he smokes joints and drinks there at
vacila de que fuma porros y bebe ahí en
the party in a short bottle and it's
el botellón en una botella corta y es
like well let's see they couldn't be they
como bueno a ver tampoco podían ser
couldn't be many many
tampoco podían ser muchas muchas
variants Uh many variants of let's see
variantes Eh muchas variantes de a ver
if it wasn't a child it was someone special
si no era un niño era alguien especial
in another way okay
de otra forma vale
and I put
y puse
another what was this guy another another another
otro qué era este tío otro otro otro al
random okay Wait to see if this is
azar vale Espera a ver si está esto
off yes I had it paid Sorry eh
apagado sí lo tenía pagado Perdona eh
Ah I can't see your
Ah no me sale tu
message I can't see your message dude
mensaje no me sale tu mensaje tío
Sorry what did it say me  you can
Perdona qué es lo que ponía me lo podéis
put it in the chat
poner en el chat
look at my t's the thing about changing
fijaros en los t mío lo de cambiar
cristinini for Mara Patio is to
cristinini por María Patiño es para
defame IB with more intensity than
funar a IB con más intensidad que el año
last year a t that is completely a
pasado un t que es completamente una
joke Well flirting a little with
broma Bueno piropeando un poco a
cristinini, it doesn't pay attention let's not say no and
cristinini no ensala no digamos no y
Philip comes and answers me about stealing
viene y me contesta Philip lo de robarse
thousands of euros from Los pamb idiots it's not
miles de euros de Los pamb idiotas no es
only to be defamed but to go to
solo para ser funados sino para ir a la
[ __ ] jail garbage I
[__] cárcel basura
mean look at what the tet was about what
o sea fijaros de lo que iba el tet de lo
he answers
que él contesta
okay This is about ander that we'll
vale Esto es lo de ander que luego lo
see later okay ibai's friend bildu voter who
veremos vale el amigo de ibai votante de
acts like a progressive And such But he hasn't
bildu que va de progre Y tal Pero no se
woken up before 4 in the afternoon
ha despertado antes de las 4 de la tarde
since 2017 he comes to talk to us about
desde 2017 viene a hablarnos de
democracy okay you didn't even finish high school
democracia vale tú ni terminaste la eso
and you come to talk to us about politics from time
y vienes a hablarnos de política de vez
to time dedicate yourself to talking about
en cuando dedícate a hablar de chismes
youtuber gossip and kissing his ass Daniel
de youtuber y a lamerle el culo Daniel
Daniel that's the best you know how to
Daniel que eso es lo mejor que sabes
do Andalusian and
hacer andaluz y
lawyer or this other one not about gorgo and
letrado o este otro no de sobre gorgo y
I'm saying gorgo  it's a wreck I do
estoy diciendo que gorgo es un despojo
n't think it'll surprise anyone blah blah
No creo que sorprenda a nadie bla bla
blah and it comes to me and it turns me on if gorgo is a
bla y me viene y me pone si gorgo es un
wreck Dalas
despojo Dalas
wh and he's not a child eh I mean he's not a
qu y no es un niño eh o sea no es un
child dude So I give a lot of
niño tío Entonces yo mucha mucha
explanation to people obsessed with
explicación a gente obsesionada con el
Dallas I see it because there are a lot of people
Dallas la veo porque hay mucha gente
obsessed like that too I mean from the
obsesionada también así O sea de de la
audience I don't know Why the truth is it's
audiencia no sé el Por qué la verdad es
worthy of study that the audience
digno de estudio que que la audiencia
because I understand that for example you say
porque entiendo que por ejemplo tú dices
Well then Someone who has belonged
Bueno pues Alguien que ha pertenecido
to his past his a former friend for
a su pasado su una un ex amigo por
example I know okay you have
ejemplo yo que sé vale que tengas ahí
a grudge there but people in the audience
una enquina pero gente de la audiencia
are
ya es
like
como
well I don't understand I don't understand But
bueno no lo entiendo No lo entiendo Pero
move eh But move move
mueve eh Pero mueve mueve
in general he's processing a ton of
en general está tramitando un montón de
complaints against all those who have
denuncias contra todos los que le han
called him a scammer for the Pambi issue and
llamado estafador por el tema pambi y
a few videos for the people who
unos cuantos vídeos para la gente que
hate me I don't believe that he's going
odia a mí no me cona que esté
through a ton of complaints But
transitando un montón de denuncias Pero
well I'm telling you I'm not up on
bueno ya te digo no estoy puesto en
all the procedures that he has and that he
todos los procedimientos que tiene y que
puts and that he carries I mean sometimes I
pone y que lleva o sea algunas veces
even find out at the same time that he
incluso me entero al tiempo de que de
had the [ __ ] of the eh lerl  I didn't
que tenía [__] la del eh lerl
know very well everything until
no supe bien bien bien todo hasta que ya
the laser started to tell it I knew I knew
empezó el láser a contarlo supe supe
something that happened I'm not going to lie to you I knew
algo que pasó no os voy a engañar supe
something that happened because the [ __ ] one day he
algo que pasó porque [__] en su día me
spoke to me host Look what they've done to me I don't
habló [__] Mira lo que me han hecho no
know how much you know but I didn't know to what extent
sé cuánto sabes pero no supe qué medida
how it was I don't know what you know I didn't know much you
cómo iba no sé qué sabes no supe mucha
know
sabes
but it's been preparing for several weeks and they will
pero lleva varias semanas preparándose y
start publishing the moves
empezará a publicar las movidas
regularly so that everything comes out at the
regularmente para que salga todo al
same time and people only focus
mismo tiempo y la gente solo se Centre
on the things that go well for them
en las cosas que le salgan bien
filed complaints that they will announce as
denuncias archivadas que anunciará como
won and dismissed trials that they will
ganadas y juicios sobreseídos que
publish as
publicará como
victories of course
victorias claro
mm if someone
mm si alguien te
reports you and they
denuncia y la
file it for you in a certain way it is a
archivan para ti de cierta forma es una
victory not a
victoria no una
peace of mind no Look it's not winning
tranquilidad no A ver no es ganar al
100% Because they may have
100% Porque pueden que te hayan
filed you because Look it is a subject that can
archivado porque Mira es un tema que ya
no longer be investigated it is a subject that I
no se puede investigar es un tema que o
mean I have seen people celebrate
sea yo he visto gente celebrar denuncias
filed or dismissed complaints And you say eh
archivadas o sobreseída Y dices tú eh
boy of course it is that what they
chico claro es que de lo que te han
reported you for they can no longer
denunciado ya no te pueden
investigate you a kiss you know it's not something
investigara un beso sabes no es como
to complain about Pea to ask for forgiveness
para reclamar Peña que te pida perdón
but oh well nothing  check it out a kiss handsome a
pero bueno na checla un beso guapo un
kiss But well It depends on how you look at it
beso Pero bueno Es depende como lo mire
but man for the person who is
pero hombre para la persona que está
being reported to have it archived or
siendo denunciada que te la archiven o
dismissed dismissed and archived is
sobreseído sobreseído y archivado es
almost the same okay What happens is that
casi lo mismo vale Lo que pasa que
archived is like definitive and
archivado es como definitivo y y
dismissed is understood to be well
sobreseido se entiende que es bueno
archived for a time or
archivado durante un tiempo o de
while well
mientras bueno
firmly dismissed also exists I mean I
sobreseído firme también existe o sea
think dismissed and archived
creo que sobreseído y archivado
mean practically the same thing uh you would have to
significa prácticamente lo mismo eh
ask Pablo what the
habría que preguntarle a Pablo Qué
difference is between one word and the
diferencia hay entre una palabra y la
other but it comes to the same thing because
otra pero viene hac lo mismo porque
provisionally archived can
archivado provisionalmente se puede
also be said I mean I don't know
decir también o sea no sé
okay But well or so of course let's see if
vale Pero bueno o sea claro a ver si al
Dallas has been reported for
Dallas lo lo han denunciado por
gender violence and the procedures
violencia de género y los procedimientos
have been that archived of course for him it is a
han que archivado claro para él es una
victory no above all it is a victory
victoria no sobre todo es una victoria
when he has had various there have been several
cuando ha tenido vari han habido varios
appeals and attempts have been made to fight You know
recursos y se ha intentado pelear Sabes
why you say Well it is that they have not been
porque tú dices Bueno es que no han
able to investigate because it is something uh
podido investigarse porque es algo eh
that has been a long time And you know for
que ha pasado mucho tiempo Y sabes por
example there is a case that I am not going to
ejemplo hay un caso del que yo no voy a
talk about okay for the moment if they want me to talk I will
hablar vale de momento si quieren que
talk but there is a case that I do
hable hablo pero hay un caso el que yo
not want to talk about uh that  archived okay
no quiero hablar eh que se archivó vale
And it's like of course it was archived because what the
Y es como claro se archivó porque qué
hell are you going to investigate something from I do
[__] vas a investigar una cosa de hace
n't know if 15 years ago or 20 years ago or 10 whatever
no sé si 15 años o 20 años o 10 lo que
okay And it was archived Of course but I don't I
sea vale Y se archivó Claro pero yo no
consider that it has been archived because
Considero que se ha archivado porque
man let's see of course you know if it has been archived yes let's see it's
hombre a ver por supuesto sabes si se ha
not the same as
archivado si a ver no es lo mismo que
archiving for a reason than it is archived
archive por un motivo a que se archive
because it cannot be investigated because there are no
porque no se pueda investigar porque no
longer ways to investigate it than
existen ya maneras de investigarlo a que
something If you
una cosa Se
appeal a thousand times and a thousand things are presented and a thousand things are presented and a
e se recurra mil veces y se presenten
thousand things are presented and still they don't
presenten mil cosas y aún así no te lo
admit it to process so that there is a
admitan a trámite como para que haya
trial not like for example the case
juicio no como por ejemplo lo del caso
of gender violence of Antonio David
de violencia de género de Antonio David
for example also no
por ejemplo también no
and there is no case okay but man for the
e no hay caso vale pero hombre para la
person who is denounced it is like a
persona que está denunciada es como una
victory Well of course of course I am going to
victoria Pues claro
go one step ahead and
voy a ir un paso por delante y a
tell you what he is preparing against
contaros lo que está preparando contra
me to save you from the lies and
mí para ahorraros las mentiras y
nonsense of his future videos pay the
desvarío de sus futuros vídeos paga los
9000 I do not have to pay the 9000 and
9000 yo no tengo que pagar los 9000 y
now that you remind me They have  sent
ahora que me lo recuerdas Me han mandado
a tweet from the lady today telling me
un tweet de la señora hoy diciéndome
accusing me that I'm going to appeal
echándome en cara que yo voy a recurrir
it
lo
to extend the two more years so
e para alargar los dos años más entonces
since the lady sees all my live streams I'm
como la señora ve todos mis directos le
going to tell her no ma'am I'm not appealing it
voy a decir no señora yo no lo recurro
to extend the two more years I have no
para alargar los dos años más no tengo
intention of extending anything I have
ninguna intención en alarg nada Yo tengo
my life my life is about other
mi vida que mi vida se trata de otras
things okay and I'm appealing it because I trust
cosas vale e yo lo recurro porque Confío
that the appeal can be changed because
en que puede cambiar el recurso porque
there are many things that have been
hay muchas cosas que han sido un
nonsense in the sentence but
disparate en la sentencia pero
of course I for example other
claro yo por ejemplo otros
procedures I have not appealed them
procedimientos No los he recurrido
because dig Ah okay well it works Cool but of
porque dig Ah vale bien sirve Guay pero
course then you Why have you appealed why are
claro entonces usted Por qué ha
you appealing the thing about the
recurrido ustedes por qué recur lo del
dog I'm going to go one step ahead and
perro voy a ir un paso por delante y a
tell you what she's preparing against
contaros lo que está preparando contra
me to save you from the lies and
mí para ahorraros las mentiras y
nonsense of her future
desvarío de sus futuros
videos Although if she decides to upload them
vídeos Aunque si se anima a subirlos
I will respond with evidence and data that
responderé con pruebas y datos que lo
disprove everything as always it's that I don't
desmientan todo como siempre es que no
understand I mean you don't know what you don't know
entiendo O sea no sabes lo que no sabes
what video is going to be Dallas you're
qué vídeo va a ser Dallas te estás
imagining what video is going to be
imaginando qué vídeo va a ser
Dallas And you're already preparing a
Dallas Y estás ya preparando una
response you don't know what it is that it doesn't have  no
respuesta no sabes a qué es que no tiene
sense it makes no sense at all there is
sentido no tiene sentido ninguno no hay
no way to get it it
no hay por dónde
's that to get it this guy right
cogerlo es que cogerlo este chico verdad
a kiss sweetheart take note he's been
un beso corazón tomad nota lleva meses
asking his panid detectives for months to
pidiendo a sus panid detectives que
collect everything they can against me
recopilen todo lo que puedan contra mí
from sarcastic tweets from years ago
desde tweet sarcásticos de hace años
to out of context responses that
hasta respuestas fuera de contexto que
are in my videos and
haya en mis vídeos y redes
social networks The idea is to make some kind
sociales La idea es hacerme una especie
of definitive video another one in which he
de vídeo definitivo otro en el que
will mix those nonsense made up stories
mezclará esas tonterías historias
that he's been told or that he
inventadas que le han contado o de las
remembers of course and as
que se acuerda por supuesto y como de
usual without proving or demonstrating anything
costumbre sin probar ni demostrar nada
today is the day the info Surely delox
hoy es el día la info Seguramente se la
is leaking it
está filtrando
clear [ __ ] well I hadn't thought of it Clear clear Yes
claro [__] pues no lo había pensado
yes it makes
sí tiene
sense no but apart from that
sentido que no pero que aparte es que
this is not
esto no
going to happen and testimonies from several girls who
vamos y testimonios de varias chicas a
I have taught a lesson on the
las que he dado un escarmiento en el
channel in series like crazy Twitter or
canal en series como locas de Twitter o
videos exposing lies and
vídeos exponiendo mentiras y
behaviors of those who wish me
comportamientos de quienes me desean la
dead and so on
muerte y demás
Ah Ricky So when they
Ah Ricky Entonces cuando a ti te
insult you on
insultan en
social media I want to see this crazy [ __ ]
redes quiero verlo de locas del [__]
because dex and Ricky come out to
este porque dex y Ricky salen a
respond to videos that Dallas has not
responder vdeos que Dallas no le ha
done the same to him delox did with the
hecho lo mismo hizo delox con el vídeo
nimu video  that never
de nimu que nunca
came out crazy Twitter But what is the
salió locas de Twitter Pero cuál es el
tone
tono
that the tone that Ricky uses in crazy
que el tono que utiliza Ricky en locas
Twitter What
de Twitter Cuál
is What has happened with with Twitter no and
es Qué ha pasado con con Twitter no y
with my name and sign I'm very sorry
con mi nombre y firmara lo siento mucho
anything you have me here Chiqui
cualquier cosa me tienes por aquí Chiqui
you said that you have two neurons
has dicho que tienes dos neuron
coca-cola of
coca-cola de
2019 beautiful the industry while you have
2019 bonito la industria mientras tú has
treated a lot of people like a piece of [ __ ]
tratado como un trozo de [__] a mucha
and I don't care if it was drugged
gente y me da igual que fuera drogado
or sober and he is accusing him of going like that
que sobrio y lo está acusando de que iba
okay
así vale
also chapter one of the crazy ones here I
además capítulo uno de las locas de aquí
realized that I had made a
me di cuenta de que había cometido un
huge mistake and I told him you're right
craso error y le dije tienes razón
Sorry I already apologized cordially and
Perdona ya me disculpe cordial y
formally as an adult that I
formalmente como persona adulta que me
consider myself and that I believe that I am and one
considero y que creo que que soy e una
thing that I found very funny and that
cosa que me ha hecho mucha gracia y que
yes I would like to comment on this
sí que me gustaría comentar en este
video is that this person is worth sir
vídeo es que esta persona vale de siré
Rodrguez that I will really say Well I
Rodríguez que de verdad de ciré yo Bueno
hope he hasn't removed it because
espero que no lo haya quitado porque
this was almost a little over a
esto hace casi hace un poco más de un
month ago from this tweet But well it is and that if
mes de este tweet Pero bueno es e que si
we go to his profile okay no I can't
nos vamos a su perfil vale no no puedo
go that I would have to look for it and
ir que tendría tendría que buscarlo y
look well okay I do
mirar bien vale
n't know if insult  I know what the
no sé si insultar no sé cuál será el
tone will be, I would have to look at it and such. The
tono tendría que mirarlo y tal e La
thing is that, of course, man, if your things
Movida es que claro hombre si tus cosas
have context, other people's things do too.
tienen contexto la de los demás también
If you get angry with someone when they
si tú te enfadas con alguien cuando te
wish you dead and maybe you
desea la muerte y a lo mejor tú le
wish them dead in return. Well, of course,
deseas la muerte de vuelta Pues claro
other people's things do too. Anyway, he'll
los de los demás también en
put these chicks up as victims of
fin pondrá a estas tías como Víctimas de
harassment, lynching, and whatever else they want to
acoso linchamiento y lo que quieren
mention, even though when I respond I
mentarse pese que cuando yo respondo
always insist that
siempre insisto en que no se ataque a
the people mentioned not be attacked, selling himself
las personas mencionadas vendiéndose
as the defender of women, although we
como el defensor de las mujeres aunque
've all already seen how he treated his
ya hemos visto todos Cómo trataba a su
last
última
girlfriend and the things he does and says about his
novia y las cosas que hace y dice de su
current
actual
partner, what he does and says about his
pareja qué es lo que hace y dice de su
partner. Well, and how he treated his
pareja Bueno y cómo trataba a su
previous girlfriend would also be interesting,
anterior novia también sería Interesante
but oh well, I
pero bueno
already know that story, but the one about his
Ese cuento ya me lo sé pero el de su
current
actual
partner, that one that's new
pareja ese eso que es nuevo
now, a tracksuit, a xenophobic
ahora t chándal tratador xenófobo
harasser, and relating it to geo, as he
acosador y relacionándola de géo como
usually does,
suele hacer
in a few days he's going to go up to Andorra to
en unos días va a subir a andorra para
ask about the
preguntar por la orden de
restraining order, how does he know this, did
alejamiento esto cómo lo sabe le ha
Dallas tell him
dicho el Dallas en alguna
somewhere, or rather, a joke, but damn it's
parte o sea una payasada pero [__] es
that  I'm freaking out
que he flipado
not in a few hours in a few days Andorra is going to upload
no en unas horas en unos días va a subir
to ask about the
andorra para preguntar por la orden de
restraining order that I requested
alejamiento que solicité el año
last year to me the thing about the
pasado a mí es que lo de la orden de
restraining order seems so roasted
alejamiento me parece tal asada
man I mean him him Why why did Ricky make that
tío o sea el el Por qué por qué puso esa
excuse he made it up but I do
excusa el Ricky eso se lo inventó pero
n't remember
no me acuerdo a cuento de
what it was about But how ridiculous is that eh the thing about the
qué Pero qué ridículo es eso eh lo de la
restraining order of course for the
orden de alejamiento claro para los
kids who follow him it
chiquillos que le siguen por un debate
wasn't a debate No because of something like he didn't want to
no fue No por algo de que no quería
debate with him
debatir con él
no but how ridiculous the thing about the
no pero qué cosa más ridícula lo de la
order of it goes that of course the people who
orden de lo pasa que claro la gente que
hate Dallas well it's
odia al Dalas pues le
worth it because they also use it as an excuse
vale porque lo coge también como excusa
even if they don't believe it deep down I
aunque no se lo crea en el fondo no
can't sleep
puedo dormir
kiss a
beso un
kiss there's a clip that went viral on
beso hay un clip que se hizo viral en
Twitter of when Dallas was reacting to
Twitter de cuando Dallas reaccionaba a
the evening where he tells Li to
la velada donde él le dice a Li de
cover up and all the haters have said that
taparse y todos los haters han dicho que
he criticized Alex for that and then he does the
él criticaba a Alex por eso y luego hace
same thing but that could be what
lo mismo va pero a eso puede ser a lo
Ricky is referring to that clip We
que se refiera Ricky ese clip lo
were watching it here I don't remember
Estuvimos viendo aquí no me acuerdo en
which excerpt And why of course let's see
qué extracto Y por qué claro a ver
and we were talking about  those click in the
e estuvimos hablando de esos click en el
sense that I do not agree
sentido de que yo no estoy de acuerdo
with the way Darl criticized Lesv
con la forma de darl de criticar a lesv
okay if I agreed with some
vale si estuve de acuerdo en algunas
things that she criticized okay I remember that
cosas que criticó vale me acuerdo que
we laughed a lot with the 10
nos reímos mucho con lo de los 10
second thing no eh
segundos no eh
but with others I think it's not worth it I
pero ya con otras creo que no vale
would have to watch again everything that was
tendría que volver a ver todo lo que se
said about Ali and so on okay But there are
habló de Ali y demás vale Pero hay hay
some things that are not worth it Of course but I
algunas cosas que no vale Claro pero
also do not agree that Dasas
tampoco estoy de acuerdo en que dasas
was doing anything wrong telling
estuviera haciendo nada malo diciendo a
Liis at that moment to cover up Not
la liis en ese momento que se tapara No
because one of her breasts was going to pop out of the
porque se le iba a salir un pecho del
dress I think it was or something like that no [ __ ]
vestido creo que era o algo así no
But extrapolate this to
[__] Pero extrapolar esto a
that I mean if you are precisely defending
eso o sea si precisamente defiendes a
Lesv from Dallas telling her that
lesv de que Dallas le haya dicho eso
our
nuestra
po did the same to Yici because it's
po lo mismo hacia el yici porque es una
nonsense since time has passed and she doesn't
chorrada como ha pasado tiempo y no
have permission to live
tiene permiso para vivir
here she has given it away others
aquí la ha regalado otros
Lauti has given away another 50
lauti ha regalado otos 50
kids Lautaro says the difference is
chavales lautaro dice la diferencia es
that As made everything up Ai never told him anything
queas inventó todo Ai nunca le dijo nada
Javi we would have to see it again but it does
Javi tendríamos que verlo de nuevo pero
sound to me that there were some
sí que me suena que hubo algunos
comments from Ali that were quite
comentarios de Ali que fueron bastante
uncomfortable I would not insinuate  abuse or
incómodo yo no insinuar un maltrato ni
anything like that okay a bad
nada por el estilo vale que un mal
temper starts off
carácter parte
very grumpy very tasty okay But of
muy cascarrabia muy saboro vale Pero por
course Not to insinuate
supuesto No insinuar un
abuse but there were some
maltrato pero sí que hubo alguna algunos
comments towards arj that I didn't
comentarios hacia arj que no me
find
parecieron ni de
acceptable okay I don't remember what it was about
recibo vale No me acuerdo de lo que iba
but it was a topic that also We laughed
pero era un tema que además Nos reímos
a lot not with the thing
mucho no con lo
that alevi had a short fuse
de que alevi era de mecha corta
but I don't remember we would have to see him again we
pero no me acuerdo tendríamos que volver
would have to
verlo tendríamos que volver a
see him again man this is pathetic eh as
verlo tío esto es patético eh como ha
time has passed and he doesn't have permission to
pasado tiempo y no tiene permiso para
live here the police will notify him of my
vivir aquí la policía le notificará mi
complaint but they will tell him that the order is at the
denuncia pero le dirá que la orden está
disposal of the
a disposición
court what a joke man I think I
judicial vaya payasada tío me parece que
saw a clip about this whether you go to the
vi un cli sobre esto sea que tú vas a la
police station and they notify you of a complaint filed
comisaría y te notifica una denuncia
a
puso hace un
year ago that is already prescribed imo not
año eso ya está prescrits imo no
archived
archivados
no let's see and that the restraining order they wo
no a ver y que la orden de alejamiento
n't be able to say anything to him because it is at the
no le van a poder decir nada porque está
disposal of the court not the police let's see
a disposición judicial no policial a ver
and what Ricky says here interest
y qué es lo que dice aquí Ricky interés
is that he comes to pick her up that she crosses the
es que venga a recogerla que pise la
border identify herself at the police station and they
frontera se identifique en comisaría y
tell her Ah  you're here good afternoon what's
le digan Ah estás aquí buenas tardes qué
going on this the fact of having put
ocurre que esto el hecho de Haber puesto
or requested a
o haber solicitado una orden de
restraining order that many people in their day
alejamiento que mucha gente en su día se
have also taken as a joke because they
la ha tomado también de broma porque
have a lot of experience with
tienen mucha experiencia en ordenes de
restraining orders I suppose that really it can't be
alejamiento Supongo que realmente no se
proven until the person against whom it is
puede probar hasta que la persona contra
filed or executed appears the
la que se interpone o se ejecuta se
interest is that they come to pick it up
persone interés es que venga a recogerla
that they cross the border they identify themselves at the
que pise la frontera se identifique en
police station and they tell them Oh you're here
comisaría y le digan Ah estás aquí
good afternoon what's going on this the
buenas tardes qué ocurre que esto el
fact of having put or requested
hecho de Haber puesto o haber solicitado
a restraining order that many people
una orden de alejamiento que mucha gente
in their day have also taken as a
en su día se la ha tomado también de
joke because they have a lot of experience with
broma porque tienen mucha experiencia en
restraining orders I suppose that
órdenes de alejamiento Supongo que
really or rather Ricky has been
realmente o sea Ricky lleva semanas
saying for weeks that Dallas the moment he
diciendo que Dallas en el momento que
steps into Andorra that he crosses the
que pise andorra que pase por la
border I'm going to tell him eh Excuse me
frontera le vo a decir eh Perdona
excuse me Ricky's restraining order
perdona la orden de alejamiento de Ricky
identify yourself at the police station man What a
identifícate en comisaría tío Qué
joke is this for children
payasada es que esto para los niños
you have to be very small to get
tienes que ser muy pequeño para que te
this right you
cuele esto
don't have to be very small to
no tienes que ser muy pequeño para que
get this right no I mean here he says
te cuele esto no O sea aquí dice
listen to him again interest is that he comes to
escucharlo otra vez interés es que venga
pick it up that he steps  the border what
recogerla que pise la frontera lo que me
interests me is that he comes to pick her up that he steps on
interesa es que venga a recogerla que
the border
pise la frontera
identify himself at the police station that they
identifi en comisaría que se
identify themselves
identifiquen
police station say Ah you are here Good
comisaría digan Ah estás aquí Buenas
afternoon Ah you are here no well I have
tardes Ah estás aquí no pues tengo una
something for you what happens is that this the fact of
cosa para ti ocurre que esto el hecho de
Having put or having requested a
Haber puesto o haber solicitado una
restraining order that many people in
orden de alejamiento que mucha gente en
their also took it as a joke because they
su se la tomó también de broma porque
have we don't take it as a joke because it's
tienen no lo tomamos de broma porque es
a joke Ricky wait Wait wait
una payasada Ricky espera Espera espera
your restraining order is here [ __ ]
tu orden de alejamiento está aquí [__]
Ah look at your order what a joke eh what a
Ah mira tu orden de vaya payasada eh sea
joke man but it's that it
menuda payasada tío pero es que verdad
seems very childish to me
que me parece muy infantil
man it seems very childish even that
tío me parece muy infantil incluso eso
[Music]
[Música]
eh your restraining order Rick
eh tu orden de alejamiento Rick
childish eh I mean you get scared of a
infantil eh o sea te acojonas de un
debate and says no it's that
debate y dice no es que
uuuy it's that I put a restraining order on him
uuuy es que le puesto una orden de
But how is it going but the thing is that
alejamiento Pero cómo le va pero es que
apart it doesn't make sense man
aparte es que no tiene sentido tío esto
Maybe it's that no it's not a problem of mine
Quizás es que no no es un problema mío
it's something between the two of them that they kill
es una cosa entre ellos dos que se maten
each other you understand
entre ellos me entiendes
But this would deserve that Dallas made
Pero esto merecería que Dallas hiciera
a good video and say Look
un buen vídeo y que diga Mira
Ricky the threats of a  Ricky No, those
Ricky las amenazas de a Ricky No esos
messages where he tells you that he's going to
mensajes no donde le dice que te le va a
rip your arm off were a year and a
arrancar un brazo fueron hace un año y
half or two ago, okay?
medio o dos vale
For a year and a half or two, Ricky
em Durante un año y medio o dos a Ricky
hasn't given a damn about those threats and not
le ha sudado la [__] esas amenazas y no
only has he given a damn
solamente es que le haya sudado la [__]
but he's been making fun of those
sino que se ha estado burlando de esas
threats publicly for a long
amenazas públicamente durante mucho
time and on top of that, he's also
tiempo y aparte le ha
dedicated several series of
e aparte le ha dedicado varias series de
videos to you
vídeos
insulting each other insulting you many times
insultándose insultándolo muchas veces
nobody respects you nobody is
nadie te tiene respeto nadie te tiene
afraid of you I don't know what
miedo no sé qué
so they're not going to give you a
entonces no te van a dar una orden de
restraining order Ricky just because you request it, that's
alejamiento Ricky porque tú la solicites
not like when you
eso no es como cuando tú
request it, I know, like if you go
solicitas que sé como si tú te vas a
buy some
comprar unas entradas de
movie tickets, I mean, imagine, and go to the police station. No,
cine o sea imagínate y a la comisaría No
look, I want a
mira que quiero una orden de
restraining order, that case has to be studied by
alejamiento eso el caso tiene estudiarlo
the judge, I mean, that's not how it works It doesn't
el juez o sea eso no funciona
even work like that I mean, you have to
así Es que ni siquiera funciona así O
be a little kid to
sea tienes que ser un niño pequeño para
believe what Ricky is saying
creerte lo que está diciendo Ricky
there, I mean, it doesn't work like that, in order for them to
ahí o sea es que no funciona así para
give you a
que para que a ti te den una orden de
restraining order, you have to have some
alejamiento tú tienes que tener unas
complaints already admitted and processed and
denuncias ya admitidas trámite y
then you request it from the court and
entonces tú lo solicitas al juz y se
the case is being studied but of course
estudia el caso pero claro ya tiene que
the case must already be in procedure, that he has
estar el caso en procedimiento queas
given his version, as well as
haya dado su versión también todo el
all that stuff and that Ricky is in danger. I mean, you have to keep in mind that a restraining order implies, uh, it's very delicate because it implies a violation in some way of the freedom of the person who is subjected to it. Imagine in this case, Dallas doesn't. I mean, yes, yes, if they
pone imagínate en este caso Dallas no O
put a
sea si si si le ponen una orden de
restraining order on him, Dallas can't be I don't know
alejamiento Dallas no puede estar no sé
how many meters around Ricky. I mean,
cuántos metros alrededor de Ricky O sea
you're somehow violating his
estás de alguna manera vulnerando su
freedom. If Ricky goes to see Titan at the movies,
libertad si Ricky va a ver Titan al cine
Dallas can't go to the movies that day. Do you
Dallas no puede ir ese día al cine me
understand? There has to be a trial, not
entiendes tiene que haber un juicio no
a trial, Sari, but a study by
un juicio Sari pero si un un estudio de
the judge, he has to evaluate it. Do you
por parte del juz lo tiene que valorar
understand? Not because he goes and
me entiendes No porque él vaya y lo
requests it and sends some
solicite y mande unas capturas de
screenshots from the discord, that doesn't
pantalla del discord es que eso no
work, so no, it doesn't work like that, not
funciona así que no que no funciona así
in Andorra or anywhere else in the
ni en andorra ni en ninguna parte del
world, that's a lie, guys, it's a
mundo que es mentira chicos que es
lie, it's an invention, but
mentira que es un invento pero es que
apart from that, it's a childish invention, I
aparte es un invento infantil
mean, it's an invention.
o sea es un es un invento al
[Music]
[Música]
level I know what your friends tell you do you
nivel Yo queé sé que te digan tus amigos
want to go down and you say Oh my mom won't
quieres bajar y tú digas Ay mi mamá no
let me my dog ate my
me deja mi perro se ha comido los
homework So it's not like that
deberes O sea que que es que no existe
he went to the police station to
eso que él haya ido a la comisaría a
file a complaint he could have done it
poner una denuncia puede haberlo hecho
the truth would be very ridiculous because of
la verdad sería muy ridículo porque
course that's what I'm telling you is what I'm saying
claro es lo que os estoy diciendo es lo
is what I'm telling you Yes I know that Ricky
es lo queos estoy Sí ya sé que Ricky
has small children of course children the
tiene niños chicos claro se niños los
small children that follow him don't give a
niños pequeños que le sigue les vale la
damn but what I'm
película pero que es lo que estoy
saying is it strange that I file a
diciendo es raro que le ponga una
complaint because of course we're
denuncia porque Claro que estamos
talking about screenshots from
hablando de que son unas capturas de
a year and a half ago I don't know if it's two and
hace un año y medio no sé si ha a dos y
during that year Ricky hasn't given a
durante ese año a Ricky le ha sudado
damn about the conversation and the
toda la [__] la conversación y las
threats but it's not only that he hasn't given a damn but he's been
amenazas pero no solamente es que le
laughing at those threats in public
riendo de esas amenazas en en público
many times So it would be as simple
muchas veces Entonces sería tan sencillo
as he files the complaint and Dallas
como le pone la denuncia y al Dallas le
gets the complaint and says but Yes this
llega la denuncia y dice pero Si este
guy is laughing at the
tío se está riendo de la de la
conversation on social media I mean when
conversación en redes O sea a mí cuando
Jo Juan's friend threatened me that
me amenazó el amigo de Jo Juan que eso
was brutal no  the messages that they
era brutal no los mensajes que me
sent me directly the same night
mandaron directamente en la misma noche
take Pablo Pablo filed the complaint the
toma Pablo Pablo puso la denuncia la
next morning pin Pam and that's it
mañana siguiente pin Pam y y ya está
but they don't put a restraining order on him
pero no le ponen una orden de
which does imply that it will be taken
alejamiento lo que sí implica que se
into account if he does it again or
tiene en cuenta si lo vuelve a hacer o
something like that okay but a restraining order
algo por el estilo vale pero una orden
that makes no
que no tiene
sense that doesn't exist like what he
sentido que no existe eso como eso que
's talking about Ricky made it up
está contando Ricky se lo ha inventado
honestly but it seems very
sinceramente que pero me parece muy
childish to me and very, very ridiculous I mean it
infantil y muy y muy ridículo O sea me
seems very ridiculous to me It seems very
parece muy ridículo Me parece muy
ridiculous and since he doesn't travel like he doesn't
ridículo y como no transita como no
reside or travel in the country
reside ni transita en el país con
frequently since they haven't found him yet they have
frecuencia al no haber dado con él aún
n't been able to activate it but How to
no la han podido activar pero Cómo que
activate or deactivate this guy who
activar o Desactivar este tío que se
thinks he has that a little button like
cree que tiene eso un un botoncito como
the iPhone to activate airplane mode and
el iPhone para Activar el modo avión y
deactivate airplane mode this guy is dumb
quitar el modo avión este tío es tonto
dude this guy really I mean the
tío este tío de verdad O sea que está la
restraining order is there okay he has it
orden de alejamiento ahí puesta vale la
but when he steps on
tiene puesta pero cuando da la pisa
Andorra it
andorra se
activates like the bluetooth on his cell phone dude
activa como el bluetooth del móvil tío
for them to approve the
para que aprueben la orden de
restraining order The judge has to assess a
alejamiento El juez tiene que valorar un
real danger if the guy doesn't live in
peligro real si el tío no vive en
Andorra they're not going to
andorra no te lo van a
give it to you it's like I  I'm putting a
dar sea es como si yo le pongo una orden
restraining order on Messi because I think he
de alejamiento a Messi [__] porque creo
can bite me at any
que me puede morder en cualquier
moment, dude, man, who's across the
momento un tío tío que está al otro lado
pond. It's ridiculous. It's ridiculous, man. It's
Charco Es ridículo Es ridículo tío Es
ridiculous, this little gang that's
ridículo la la pandillita esta que se
forming against Dallas,
está haciendo en contra del Dallas de
really, very
verdad muy
special. Hey Javi, I just came to say
especialita Hola Javi solo vine a
hello, handsome. I love you, I love you. That's it. Thank you
saludar guapo Te quiero yo te quiero eso
very much. He'll
Muchas
use this to say that the
gracias utilizará esto para decir que la
order doesn't exist instead of that it's not
orden no existe en lugar de que no está
active and me and me and me, man. And he won't
activa y yo y yo y yo tío y no
mention the rest of the complaint
mencionará el resto de la denuncia
because he knows that without being a resident he doesn't
porque sabe que sin ser residente no
need to take action
necesita tomar medidas al respecto ya
since nothing can happen to him. Sad but
que no le puede pasar nada triste pero
true, if I receive it and
cierto en caso de recibirle y
respond to it, a trial will be held where I
responderla se celebrará un juicio donde
will present new direct attacks and
presentaré nuevos ataques directos y
recent death threats that he has
amenazas de muerte recientes que me ha
made to me through third parties who have
dedicado mediante terceros que han
had contact with him lately. Man, what a
tenido contacto con él últimamente tío
pathetic thing,
Qué cosa más patética
man, what a pathetic thing,
tío Qué cosa más patética
these third parties come in,
en esos terceros entrad delos
presenting themselves as witnesses. That's the
presentándose de testigo Esa es la
move, very well, very well, very well, have you
movida muy bien muy bien muy bien habéis
been attentive, I'm not well, I'm not well, you are
estado atento yo estoy malillo estoy
my Helena, I'm not well and I
malillo estáis mi Helena estoy malillo y
'm not very, very fine Elena Elena
no estoy muy muy fino Elena
are you there
Elena estás ahí
Elena What's Elena doing today we had some
Elena Qué hace Elena hoy hemos tenido
very sad news for  Your Honor, I'll
una noticia muy triste para la señoría
say it tomorrow and it is that JJ has passed away.
lo diré mañana y es que ha fallecido JJ
JJ, surely if you are around here a lot you will
JJ seguramente si estáis por aquí mucho
know her. Well, she has been a
la conoceréis bueno que ha sido
collaborator in fact some nights she has
colaboradora de hecho algunas noches ha
gone up to, she has gone up to the live shows with
subido a ha subido a los directos con
us, she has gone up to the live shows with
nosotros ha subido los directos con
us and I found out that she has
nosotros y me he enterado que ha
passed away. The truth is that I was
fallecido la verdad que me Me he quedado
shocked eh because I didn't
flipando eh porque no
know, I didn't know that the woman was ill. I don't think she
sabía no sabía que estaba mal a la mujer
was very old. I don't know what
creo que no era muy mayor no sé qué es
happened but apparently
lo que habrá pasado pero por lo visto
there are relatives who have
hay familiares que se han puesto en
contacted her. Gentlemen, I have to
contacto con con la señoreros tengo que
see it, I have to see it tomorrow
verlo tengo que verlo mañana
calmly because I found out
tranquilamente porque me me enterado
now on my way to my house, ditia, don't
ahora viniendo para mi casa ditia no me
tell me, [ __ ] what the
diga [__] qué
hell, what the hell but she wasn't a very
palo qué palo pero no era una mujer muy
old woman. I don't know what
mayor no sé qué habrá
happened. I don't know what happened, the truth is.
pasado no sé qué habrá pasado la verdad
So tomorrow we will find out and we
Así que mañana nos enteraremos y lo
will comment on it on telesalseo
comentaremos en telesalseo
but I have to, let's go. I hope that they are not
pero tengo que vamos yo espero que no me
trolling me with an issue like this because I
estén troleando con un tema así porque
think, I don't think that they have sent me
creo que no creo que me me han mandado
emails and things so I understand that it will not
email y cosas entonces entiendo que no
be
será un
trolling, I don't know what it will be because I already told you
troleo no sé qué será porque ya te digo
that let's go. I had it on WhatsApp and the
que vamos yo la tenía en WhatsApp y la
photo of the woman  she was a woman she wasn't
foto de la mujer no era una mujer no era
a very old woman The truth is yes yes JJ
una mujer muy mayor La verdad sí sí JJ
come on she was sick but you knew it why
vamos estaba malita pero lo sabíais
shame Why shame
ustedes porque lástima Por qué lástima
Well tomorrow we send a kiss to the
Bueno mañana le mandamos un beso a la
family from telesalseo that surely has a
familia desde telesalseo que seguramente
better chance of arriving
tenga más posibilidad de que llegue
From there but what a shame What a
Desde allí pero qué pena Qué
shame What a shame Ricki too eh I
pena Qué pena da ricki también eh
also tell you eh within my
También te digo eh dentro de mis
predictions I'm sure that he is still
predicciones estoy seguro de que sigue
trying to convince my
intentando convencer a mi
ex to manipulate his
ex para manipular su
testimony from a year ago and expose it on
testimonio de hace un año y exponerlo en
his channel since he thinks that the story of a
su canal ya que piensa que el relato de
girl who plays the victim while he
chica que se haga la víctima mientras él
is by her side as support is his best
está a su lado como apoyo es su mejor
basis well Ricky I have to tell you from
basa bueno Ricky tengo que decirte desde
here that Ali's thing is no longer a serious
aquí que lo de Ali ya no es que sea gra
victim my eyes bled with the Raya
vítima me sangraron los ojos con el Raya
that you put
que pusiste
XD Hey but look I put the Raya right I
XD Oye pero mira el raya lo puse yo bien
put the Raya right and being
el raya lo puse Yo bien y estando en
live they made me change it I didn't
directo me hicieron cambiarlo no hecho
realize I changed it quickly said okay p and
cuenta lo cambié rápidamente di vale p y
And now it turns out that they have eaten my
Y ahora resulta que me han comido la
comments box people telling me
caja de comentarios la gente diciéndome
that I had put it wrong I'm a
que que la había puesto mal estoy un
little sleepy laete
poquito a dormir laete
Still to  see regarding this says no
Todavía a ver respecto a esto dice no
Lali that she should play the victim Lali is a
Lali que se haga la víctima Lali es
victim Lali is a
víctima Lali sí es
victim okay you may like her more you
víctima vale os puede caer mejor os
may like her less But Lali
puede caer peor Pero Lali
is a victim, I mean Lali has a
es víctima o sea Lali tiene una
sentence from the court of violence against
sentencia del juzgado de la violencia de
women okay We have heard
la mujer vale Nosotros hemos escuchado
all versions here
aquí todas las versiones
eh
eh
but finally justice has ruled in her favor I do
pero finalmente la justicia le ha dado
n't know if there have been appeals
razón no sé si ha habido recursos
regarding that to the Supreme Court the truth
respecto a eso del al supremo la verdad
but for now there are two
pero de momento van dos
instances I had the first sentence
instancias yo la primera sentencia La
and I had the first sentence Of course, of course you have to keep
tuve y a mí la primera sentencia Claro
in mind
claro ten que hay que tener en cuenta
that they are facts that
que son hechos que
eh that are facts that are clear It's that
eh que son hechos que se claro Es que
for me that those types of trials I
para mí ese tipo de de juicios yo
trusted that they work in another way
confiaba en que funcionan de otra manera
because of course when you are denouncing
porque claro cuando tú estás denunciando
something from the past and your complaint is
una cosa del pasado y tu denuncia está
based
basada
on your complaint is based on testimonies
en tu denuncia está basada en
practically it is that
testimonios prácticamente es que
condemning based on
condenar en base a
testimonies does not end up adding up to me I have
testimonios no me termina a m de de
not had the second
cuadrar no he tenido la segunda
sentence I asked Ali for it and he did not send it to me
sentencia se la pedí al Ali y no me la
eh And and I would like to see it to see what the
eh Y y me gustaría verlo a ver qué es lo
hell is escaping me
que [__] se me escapa
there they have given her the reason solely because I am a
ahí le han d la razón únicamente por ser
woman I do not want to think that The
mujer que no quiero pensar eso La
truth is I want to have some confidence  in
verdad quiero tener cierta confianza en
justice apart from the fact that he will be eating his
justicia aparte de que estará comiendo
head with the promotion that this
la cabeza con la promoción que sería ese
video would be for his only fan and blah blah blah
vídeo para su only fan y bla bla bla
like he does with other girls that he
como hace con otras tías a las que
intends to use, I already screwed up the video The
pretende utilizar ya le jodí el vídeo La
first time I leaked that it had been
primera vez que filtré que lo habían
recorded and I hope this tweet doesn't
grabado y espero que este tweet no lo
ruin it a second time Eh dasas he hasn't
arruine una segunda Eh dasas no ha
recorded any video with Lali okay I mean I don't
grabado ningún vídeo con Lali vale o sea
know why Rick is making up that they
no sé por qué Rick aquí se inventa que
had recorded it and he hated them I mean
que lo habían grabado y él los odió o
this is pathetic
sea esto es patético
eh I am very proud to have
eh estoy muy orgulloso en haber
collaborated in exposing and uncovering the type
colaborado en exponer y destapar al tipo
of person that this guy is it
de persona que es este tipo
seems to me I have nothing
a mí me parece yo no tengo nada en
against Ricky but the truth is with this
contra Ricky pero la verdad con este
issue that I find very pathetic man
tema que se me hace muy patético tío
Total that Pablo has put him
Total que Pablo le ha puesto
directly Hello Ricky I think you have
directamente Hola Ricky creo que tienes
some problem to notify Dallas or
algún problema para notificar a Dallas o
that's what I understand from your posts if you want
eso creo entender de tus post si quieres
Tell your lawyer that it can be
Coméntale a tu abogado que se puede
notified at the address of my office
notificar en la dirección de mi despacho
I promise to notify him my
yo me comprometo a notificarle mi
phone number is very easy for you to
teléfono lo tienes muy fácil para
get it delox himself has it
conseguirlo delox mismo lo tiene un
greetings e Ricky here he
saludo e Ricky para aquí lo
has it here he has it
tiene para aquí lo tiene
Ricky there where are they
Ricky ahí dónde están la
Pablo broke it  But because it's a lie
Pablo lo partió Pero porque es mentira
guys it's a lie that there are no
chicos que es mentira que no hay órdenes
restraining orders and that there's
de alejamiento y que no hay
nothing man let's see I don't really know what's
nada hombre a ver no sé muy bien Cuál es
the deal that Ricky has with Dallas I'm
el rollo que lleva Ricky con Dallas me
missing 90 by the lords but in
pierdo el 90 por de los lores pero en
what you've posted Here I have detected at
esto que has puesto Aquí he detectado al
least two lies and it's not that you have
menos dos mentiras y no es que las hayas
detected them it's that I know that they are lies
detectado es que sé que son mentiras
But I suppose that the fights on YouTube
Pero supongo que las peleas en YouTube
are like that it's a
son así es que es
lie it's a lie I do
mentira es que es mentira
n't know but come on that thing that d carries them I do
no sé pero vamos eso de que d las lleva
n't know how much preparing lawsuits against
no sé cuánto preparando demandas contra
everyone Christ man I suppose I would
todo Cristo hombre Supongo que yo lo
know no and about the
sabría no y lo de la orden de
restraining order Well neither but come on if there is
alejamiento Pues tampoco pero vamos si
a resolution that he releases it
hay alguna resolución que la saque
even if it's anonymized and we analyze it or
aunque sea anonimizada y la analizamos o
that he gives the address of my office and I take
que dé la dirección de mi despacho y yo
responsibility for notifying dala and
me responsabilizo de notificar a dala y
answer dala I'm afraid of Ricky
contesta dala a Ricky le tengo miedo
because his nose is growing more and more from
porque cada vez le crece más la nariz de
the amount of lies he tells and one
la cantidad de mentiras que dice y un
day he will go around the planet and
día le dará la vuelta al planeta y se la
shove it right up his ass and I don't want to
meterá Así mismo por el culo y no quiero
see it he makes up literally everything and let's
verlo se inventa literalmente todo y a
see if it's true that I'm the one who
ver si ha cierto que yo es que se la ha
made it up  look how funny that a
inventado fijaos Qué gracioso que hace
few months ago he made up that I had
unos meses se inventó que yo había
recorded a video with his ex and he was going to
grabado un vídeo con su ex y lo iba a
publish it and now that everyone saw that I
publicar y ahora que todos vieron que
never published anything, he says I ruined the
jamás publiqué nada pues dice le jodí el
video with my tweet. So it's a
vídeo con mi tweet O sea que es
lie, it's a lie, man, it's
mentira es que es mentira tío es que es
an objective fact, eh, it's
un es un hecho objetivo eh
an objective fact that
es que es un hecho objetivo que es una
what Ricky is saying is a lie
mentira lo que está diciendo
but apart from that, it's a
Ricky pero ap parte que es un cuento
very childish story, the truth is that the interest is that he
como muy infantil verdad interés es que
comes to pick her up, that she crosses the border, that she
venga a recogerla que pise la frontera
identifies herself at the police station and they tell her,
se identifique en comisaría y le digan
Oh you're here, good afternoon, what's going on,
Ah estás aquí buenas tardes qué ocurre
this, the fact of having put or
que esto el hecho de Haber puesto o
requested a
haber solicitado una orden de
restraining order that many people in their day
alejamiento que mucha gente en su día se
also took it as a joke because they have
la tomó también de broma porque tienen
a lot of experience with
mucha experiencia en ordenes de
restraining orders. I suppose that it really can't be
alejamiento Supongo que realmente no se
proven until, no, it's not, it's not
puede probar hasta No no es no es
experience that any adult
experiencia que cualquier persona adulta
knows that that doesn't work, no matter what you
sabe que eso no funciona así sea tú
imagine, don't come, let's ask for
imagínate no venga vamos a pedir órdenes
restraining orders there with all the shovels, don't
de alejamiento ahí a a punta pala no
come everyone asking for
venga todo el mundo pidiendo órdenes de
restraining orders to Tok here and whoever I
alejamiento a Tok que aquí y el que yo
don't want to step foot in Seville, he's not going to
no quiera que pise Sevilla no lo va a
step foot in it, go [ __ ] yourself okay, I'm going  a I'm going to
pisar a tomar por culo vale voy a voy a
travel to Disneyland next month and I'm
viajar a Disneylandia el mes que viene y
going to have him all to myself
lo voy a tener solito para m órdenes de
restraining orders for too
alejamiento para too
kki tremendous pathetic tremendous pathetic
kki tremendo patético tremendo patético
Let's see let's talk a little let's
A ver vamos a hablar un poco vamos a
talk a little about the
hablar un poco sobre lo de los
influencers who have come out to defend
influencer que han salido a defender a
maduro look
maduro mira de
really look
verdad mira de
really
verdad
okay look really this clip for
vale mira de verdad este clip por
example is being super
ejemplo está siendo super
applauded I've never seen so many
aplaudido nunca había visto a tantos
streamers comment on complicated political issues
streamers opinar de temas políticos
so openly like
complicados de manera tan abierta como
this and some with big slips
este y algunos con patinadas gordas
eh But well I guess it's easy not
eh Pero bueno Supongo que es fácil no
when everyone supports you say whatever
cuando todo el mundo te apoya digas lo
when you already know where the
que o sea cuando ya sabes a dónde va la
current is going and when it
corriente y cuando
also benefits you
además te beneficia
eh it's very simple then when they
eh es muy sencillo luego cuando
bomb children in Gaza damn nobody says
bombardean niños en gaza [__] nadie dice
anything nobody talked about the war in
nada nadie hablado de la de la guerra en
Gaza eh nobody nobody nobody nobody has
gasa eh nadie nadie nadie nadie ha
talked about that
hablado de de eso
eh as far as I know as far as I know
eh hasta donde yo sé hasta donde yo sé
everyone talked about the issue of Gaza
todo el mundo hablado del tema de gasa
okay And I think that the victims,
vale Y yo creo que las víctimas sobre
especially if we're talking about children,
todo si estamos hablando de niños se
lament whether they are
lamentan tanto si son
Israelis or Palestinians or whatever
e israelíes como Palestina como lo que
okay obviously And more so if they are
sea vale evidentemente Y más si son
children, not the victims  always no but the
niños no las víctimas siempre no pero la
thing here is that Well here I've
movida aquí es que Bueno aquí me ha
fallen a little bit I've fallen a little bit
caído un poco me ha caído un poquillo de
of prog greenland no because I put Don
de prog grenlandia no porque puse Don
Ander it's that look at it Don Ander Corts
ander es que miral lo Don ander Cortés
no and the people were like I expend a lot of
no y estaba la gente como expendo mucho
this I say friend deb
esto digo amigo deb votante de
Bildu voter that openly Bildu voter
bildu que votante de bildu abiertamente
eh And the thing about not waking up before such and
eh Y lo de que no se ha despertado antes
such is not because look you can
de la tal no es porque a ver tú puedes
wake up every day at night
despertarte todos los días por la noche
and slept until so many because your
y dormí hasta las tantas porque tu
work in the afternoon or so what I
trabajo por la tarde o sea lo que quiero
mean by this is that they are all like the
decir con esto es que que son todos como
same No in fact something happened in the
iguales No de hecho pasó algo en los
last few days that was the clear
últimos días que que era el claro
example man it was the clear example of what I
ejemplo tío era el claro ejemplo de lo
said the night before okay look the
que dije la noche antes vale mira la
night before I had surgery I said this
noche antes de operarme dije esto
look right now the parties that are on the
mira ahora mismo los partidos que hay
left right now eh they use
isquierda ahora mismo eh utilizan los
ideals this is my opinion eh I
ideales esto es una opinión mía eh yo
think they use
creo que utilizan los ideales de
leftist ideals socially okay eh to
izquierda socialmente vale eh para
capture people but then no it is not
captar a la gente pero luego no lo no es
what they carry out it is simply
lo que llevan a cabo es simplemente un
posturing okay the issue feminism
postureo vale el tema feminismo
socialism of course to collectivize Yes  that's what I
socialismo claro para colectivizar Sí es
think, I'm not the
lo que yo pienso tampoco que yo sea el
most expert on these issues, you know, you don't
más experto en estos tema sabes tampoco
know that I don't get too involved, but that's
sabéis que no me meto muchísimo pero es
the idea that I have. You know why they are
la idea que se me da Sabes porque son
socialists and communists, with the others,
socialistas y comunistas con los demás
not with them, you understand. So of course,
no con ellos me entiendes Entonces claro
there then they are not your ideals, you do not
ahí entonces no son tus ideales no
have those ideals truly, that is
tienes esos ideales verdaderamente eso
called populism in fact, okay, I mean, that
se llama populismo de hecho vale o sea
's what you go around proclaiming And you are supposed to
es lo que vas eh proclamando Y se supone
defend but not because you feel it
que defiendes pero no porque lo sientas
but because it looks nice to win the
sino porque queda bonito para ganarte el
vote of the people who are shorter, I do
voto de la gente que es más cortita a mí
not like any party 100%, I mean,
no me gusta ningún partido al 100% o sea
I would not break my face, I would never
yo no me partiría la cara Nunca ni
argue with people over party
discutiría con la peña por partido
because I don't give a damn about apy,
porque me la sudan la apy a todos
obviously, all of them, within those that there are, well,
evidentemente dentro de los que hay pues
I vote for the one that I think is the one with which
Yo voto al que me parece que es con el
I would be better off and with which Spain
que yo estaría mejor y con el que España
would be better off, no more, okay And it's my
estaría mejor sin más vale Y es mi
opinion and I vote okay, but really.
opinión y yo voto vale pero realmente
Well, as you already understand, well, I do not vote nor will I
Pues como ya entenderéis pues no voto ni
ever vote for one of the
votaré jamás a a uno de los partidos de
two main left-wing parties that there are
izquierda dos principales que hay ahora
right now, not in Spain, never in my life,
mismo no en España jamás en la vida
never in my life, of the left-wing parties that there are
jamás en la vida de los partidos que hay
right now, never in
de izquierda ahora mismo jamás en la
life and I can have many ideals eh that
vida y puedo tener muchos ideales eh que
are more left-wing of course we
sean más de izquierda claro es que
qualify that there are ideas that do not have to
calificamos que hay ideas no que tienen
be left or right-wing no
que ser de izquierda o de derecha no
like for example the issue of eh being in
como por ejemplo el tema de eh estar a
favor because to defend women it
favor porque por defender a la mujer no
is not like you do not have to be left-wing to
es como no tienes que ser de izquierda
defend women what
para para defender a la mujer lo que
happens is that the left has appropriated
pasa es que la izquierda se ha apropiado
that only they are the
de de que solamente ellos son los
defenders of women but simply to
defensores de la mujer pero simplemente
make a little mafia with that
para para hacer un poco de mafia con ese
roll okay without more I mean we have Iren
rollo vale sin más O sea tenemos a iren
Montero calling abusers people who
Montero Llamando maltratador a gente que
are not abusers and eating sentences
no es maltratador y comiéndose condenas
of 18,000 turkeys that's why I understand em
de 18,000 pavos por eso me entiend em
But I do not believe that there is a
Pero yo no creo que hayan partido de
right-wing party that is against
derecha que esté en contra de los
women's rights in fact for me
derechos de la mujer de hecho para mí
right now the party that is called the
ahora mismo el partido al que llaman
extreme right is the party that
extrema derecha es el partido que
toughens the sentences for abusers
endurecer la penas para maltratadores
rapists eh In fact of the
violadores eh De hecho los partidos de
left-wing parties that exist right now the two
izquierda que hay ahora mismo los dos
main ones only know how to free
principales solamente saben liberar
rapists you know I mean it's the
violadores sabes O sea que es todo lo
opposite eh Well then look at this look at this you see this
contrario eh Bueno pues mirar esto mirar
This is an actor from La
esto veis este Este es un actor de de La
who  avecina No if I'm not mistaken he
que se avecina No si no me equivoco no
's not an actor from La que se avecina
es un actor de La que se avecina
no well Well it turns out
no bueno Pues resulta
that this man who was saying things
que este hombre que iba diciendo cosas
like this about squatters not all
como estas sobre los ocupas no todos los
Spaniards have the right to enjoy
españoles tienen derecho a disfrutar de
decent and adequate housing okay And he
una vivienda digna y adecuada vale Y
was against desocupa and all
estaba en contra de desocupa y todas
this nonsense has
estas movidas
not been
no ha sido
convicted he has been convicted because they
condenado ha sido condenado porque le
occupied his property they occupied his
ocuparon una propiedad le ocuparon una
property and the guy instead took
propiedad y el tío ha cogido en vez
Call Dani from desocupa which is what
Llamar a Dani de desocupa que es lo que
I would do Well the guy took in
yo haría Pues el tío ha acogido se
four friends hooded no and he
encapuchao cuatro colegas no y se ha
went in and got the squatters out Stick
metido y ha sacado los ocupas a Palo
okay or so tremendous tremendous okay of course that
vale o sea tremendo tremendo vale claro
's what I'm telling you I mean they are they are very
es lo que te digo o sea son son son muy
progressive no and very with society and very
progres no y muy con la sociedad y muy
empathetic with the world at least at least
empáticos con el mundo menos menos
when when they go through it like this
cuando cuando lo pasan
I am also very clear that
así Yo también tengo muy claro que pago
I pay the penalty no no if I had done the
yo la pena no no si yo hubiera hecho lo
same thing what happens is that I don't say
mismo lo que pasa es que yo no digo
this nonsense you know Because later
estas tonterías sabes Porque después
when I posted this tweet people came to me and
cuando he puesto este twit me han venido
said Javi but I but that
la gente a decir Javi pero yo pero que
I would do it but that I would do it
yo lo haría pero que yo lo haría
I  would and not only would I do it bu
yo lo haría y no solamente lo haría bu
It's that what I would do would be Call
Es que yo lo que haría sería Llamar a
Dani for sure okay but of course don't go around
Dani seguro vale pero claro no vayas
saying that you need them so well that we don't
diciendo que los ocupas tn bien que no
have to kick them out what blah blah blah you
hay que echarlo que patatín que patatán
're not telling me
no me estáis diciendo lo
[Music]
[Música]
about the rebor thing no that he answered To Anders
de lo de rebor no que contestó A anders
no good to everyone
no buena a todos
bu So let's go now with rivor which
bu Así vamos ahora con rivor el cual
would answer Ander like this begins First
respondería a ander así comienza Primero
I would like to make a small aside okay a
me gustaría hacer un pequeño inciso vale
very brief little aside it is very brief
un pequeño inciso muy breve es muy breve
and it is totally respectful Okay all
y es totalmente respetuoso Okay todos
those who uh dedicate their double morality to
los que eh dedican su doble moralidad a
saying is that there are people who are talking
decir es que hay gente que está hablando
about
de
Venezuela idiot or what idiot idiot or what It's that he does
Venezuela bobo o qué bobo bobo o qué Es
n't talk about Palestine the thing about Israel and
que no habla de Palestina lo de Israel y
Palestine is not from today I understand
Palestina no es de hoy yo yo entiendo
that you watch television and all Okay and they
que tú ves la televisión y tal Okay y te
give you the news but the thing is that this is not from
ponen noticias pero es que esto no es de
2 years ago it's not that it is more than 40
hace 2 años no es que tiene más de 40
years old so that you understand me it is more than
años para que me entiendas tiene más de
40 we are not talking about No look no no no no
40 no estamos hablando de No mira no no
no it's that there is a lot there is a lot goodbye loser
no no no es que hay mucho hay mucho adió
wait teeto like that they won't come back
pringado espérate teeto así no vuelven
never [ __ ] comes from a long
nunca [__] viene desde hace
time ago okay, I mean it's not from today,
bastante tiempo vale o sea no es de hoy
on the other hand, Venezuela is from today and
en cambio Venezuela es de hoy y por
unfortunately those people who are talking about
desgracia esa gente que está hablando de
the Gaza Strip, me and I, the
la franja de gaza yo y yo la franja de
Gaza Strip and the Congo, you don't have a [ __ ]
gaza y lo de Congo no tienes ni [__]
clue, right, of what's happening in
idea verdad de lo que está pasando en
Congo, no, no. Of course, since it's not
Congo no a que no Claro es que como no
publicized then you don't find out,
está publicitado entonces no te enteras
but in the Congo you see a G for
pero en el Congo está viendo un G por
example but since it's Africa Then there's no
ejemplo pero como es África Entonces no
[ __ ] in Haiti, in Haiti, what
hay un [__] en Haití en Haití que hablé
I talked about about the main Channel in Haiti. No
yo del Canal principal en Haití No
massive bombing, no, then you don't
bombardeo masivo no entonces ahí no te
find out there. Going a little deeper, I would
enteras profundizando un poquito más
say that making comparisons with those
diría que hacer comparaciones con ese
types of situations is something that is not
tipo de situaciones pues es algo que no
right and that I see as absolute nonsense.
está bien y que lo ve un absoluto sin
On the other hand,
sentido que por otra parte estar con
making comparisons about who suffers
haciendo comparativa sobre Quién sufre
the most seems despicable to me, it seems
más me parece deleznable me parece
absurd and senseless. I mean, it makes
absurdo y sin sentido O sea no tiene
no sense what's happening, is it
ningún sentido Qué pasa que hay que
necessary to position oneself politically or ideologically when it comes to Human Rights? Well, no, no, because there is a current problem in the world. Good point, also, many Spanish communists have never met or spoken with a Venezuelan, here in Chile, I have
con algún venezolano acá en Chile he
met too many  and everyone tells you that
conocido demasiados y todos te dicen que
Maduro is [ __ ] with eyes let's see man for
maduro es caca con ojos a ver tío por
God's sake you have to position yourself with
Dios tienes que posicionar por [__]
an ideology okay And it doesn't come out of
en una ideología vale Y no me sale de la
me I will never position myself with a
yo nunca me voy a posicionar con una
specific ideology it's not going to happen what I
ideología en concreto no va a ocurrir lo
can tell you for example about
que sí puedo decirte por ejemplo de
Spain what I can tell you Pablo
España lo que sí puedo decirte Pablo
Iglesias Juan Carlos Monero Irena
Iglesias Juan Carlos monedero irena
Montero all these people are each one of
Montero toda esta gente sois cada uno de
you are employees of that
vosotros sois asalariados de ese régimen
infamous regime employees on salary from the
infame asalariados a sueldo desde el
beginning I already had you identified
principio yo ya os tenía identificados
when you started to take over a
cuando empezasteis adueñar de la una
kind of revolt okay demonstrations
especie de revuelta vale manifestaciones
that took place at the time in Spain took
que hubo en su momento en España lo
advantage of it and said No no it's us we are us we are
aprovecharon y dijeron No no es nos
not so You have to
somos nosotros somos nosotros no so Hay
be an imbecile not to condemn what
que ser imbécil para no condenar lo que
Maduro is doing or defend it because it
está haciendo maduro o defenderlo porque
benefits you because it is in your interest
te sale a beneficio porque te interesa
Because if we go because you would be interested
Porque si vamos porque te interesaría
if here in Spain it was the same because you would
que aquí en España fuera lo mismo porque
be part of the votes that was
formarías parte de de la votos eso era
the people the Spanish citizenship but you didn't
la gente la ciudadanía española pero no
have to take ownership of it and I don't know
tuvisteis que adueñar de ello y no sé
how the [ __ ] you did it But as
cómo [__] lo habéis hecho Pero a medida
time goes by you have
que transcurre el tiempo os habéis
consolidated in power you have
consolidado en el poder os habéis
consolidated yourselves you have been consolidating yourselves
consolidando os habéis ido consolidando
in such an absurd way so absurd and
de una forma tan Absurda tan Absurda y
sick that you do not let go no you are not
enfermiza que no soltás no no sois
capable of letting go of what you have touched
capaces de soltar lo que habéis tocado
with your shady dealings and a thousand that you
con vuestros chanchullos y mil que
have done we have a couple of things
habéis hecho tenemos un par de cositas
from Juan brutal eh brutal this no eh I
de Juan brutal eh brutal esto no eh
wanted to comment what happens is that already Ah
quería comentar lo que pasa es que ya Ah
Lorena is waiting for me but at least this extract we are
Lorena pero por lo menos este ex tracto
going to treat it because this
sí lo vamos a tratar porque esto me
seems fabric to me no I mean Look eh There are several
parece tela no O sea Mira eh Hay varios
streamers and several creators well
streamers y varios creadores bueno
creators no who are like
creadores no que están como
defending maduro okay look for
defendiendo a maduro vale mira por
example this pipa that this pipa
ejemplo el pipa este que el pipa este
had to delete and apologize to
tuvo que borrar y pedir perdón a
Cristina continue because she put up an
Cristina seguir porque puso una
outrage which is a mantra that
barbaridad que es un mantra que defiende
the left defends Twitter okay
la izquierda Twitter vale
and the guy just said some nonsense that
e y el tío le só una burrada que dice
many people say about the band no against
mucha gente de de la banda no contra
Cristina which is not true And he had to
Cristina que no es verdad Y tuvo que
delete and apologize because let's go if not he would get
borrar y pedir perdón porque vamos si no
a sentence
le le caería una condena
beautiful never a communist will talk to you about
guapa nunca un comunista te hablará de
China and Tibet Yes yes  but it's just
China y el tibet Sí sí pero es justo
like what rebn said it's like eh
como lo que ha dicho rebón es como eh
what nobody's talking about the
qué que nadie habla de de los niños de
gasa children what the [ __ ] are you saying are we
gasa que qué [__] estás contando estamos
talking about what's happening
hablando ahora de lo que está pasando
now but apart from that yes it has been talked about no
ahora pero aparte sí se ha hablado no
well I've had a lot of tweets plus
bueno me han salido muchos tweets además
viral yes okay comparing This video of
viral yos vale comparando Este vídeo de
Luisita comunica in which she is
Luisita comunica en el que está
condemning Okay eh Look Luisito comunica
condenando Vale eh Mira Luisito comunica
denounces Nicols Maduro for the
denuncia Nicolás Maduro por la
construction of two maximum
construcción de dos cárceles de máxima
security prisons where those
seguridad donde estarán presos aquellas
people who speak out against the
personas que se presen en contra del
regime will be imprisoned okay And the saska with 4000 likes
régimen vale Y el saska con 4000 likes
is
es
Luisito comunica went to El Salvador to
Luisito comunica fue al El Salvador para
lick Bukele's boots for
lamerle las botas a bukele por vulnerar
systematically violating the human rights of
sistemáticamente los derechos humanos de
thousands of people without a
miles de personas sin juicio
prior trial, in other words he's comparing putting
previo o sea está comparando que metan
gang members in jail and rescuing El
pandilleros y rescaten El
Salvador gang members rapists who
Salvador pandilleros violadores que
have
tienen en sus historiales decenas cada
dozens of rapes, murders, assaults, and
uno de violaciones asesinatos agresiones
torture on their records with maduro making a prison
torturas con que maduro haga una cárcel
to put everyone who is against
para meter a todo el que esté en contra
who speaks out against the
que se exprese en contra del
regime and there are 4000 turkeys who have given it
régimen y hay 4000 pavos que le han dado
like 4000  turkeys that have given likes
like 4000 pavos que le ha dado a like
and tweets like these there are a few eh I
y twits como estos hay unos cuantos eh
've seen a lot eh Total that I have
Me he visto un montón eh Total que le he
posted this tweet half joking no half
puesto este twit medio broma no medio
joking half true imagine carrying your
broma medio verdad imaginaos gestar a tu
child for 9 months raising him educating him
hijo durante 9 meses criarlo educarlo
pampering him spending money so that he can go
mimarlo gastarte dinero en que pueda ir
to school so that he has a
al colegio en que tenga un plato
hot meal every day dedicating every day to
caliente cada día dedicar cada día en
teaching him values so that when he grows
enseñarle valores para que cuando sea
up he will do Call pipa on Twitter and
mayor se haga Llamar pipa en Twitter y
post these
ponga estas
things so he has stayed first
cosas total que se ha quedado de primero
quiet all afternoon he has
callao durante toda la tarde se ha
remained caini and you know what he has
quedado caini y sabéis que es lo que ha
done dude it's the typical one they are
hecho tío es la típica que son de
really they are bitter but I mean it doesn't make
verdad son unos ardidos pero o sea sin
sense
sentido
okay Where is Where is Where is the
vale Dónde está Dónde está Dónde está la
answer ratio for
respuesta ratio por
[ __ ] and it tells me a fault that I should be
subnormal y me pone un fallo de que a m
condemned for insulting a
me condenen por insultar a una
person the context doesn't
persona no importa el contexto no
matter why you have responded
importa Por qué le hayas contestado tú
with insults to that person it doesn't
con insultos a esa persona no
matter he gives you the sentence what does that have to do with it
importa te pone la condena qué tendrá
Ah Well I don't know but he's already
que ver Ah Pues no lo sé pero ya te está
telling you ratio and calling you [ __ ]
diciendo ratio y llamándote subnormal
which is as if you find insults very bad
que es como si te parecen muy mal los
and don't insult  I'm
e no insultes
not saying okay I'm saying no And of course 1000
no digo yo vale digo yo no Y claro 1000
likes suddenly and of course this guy eh
likes de repente y claro este pavo eh
these people will have had some group I don't
esta gente habrán tendrán algún grupo no
know if it's on Discord or Telegram or something
sé si de discord de Telegram alguna cosa
and they will have said let's do this let's do
y habrán dicho vamos a hacer esto vamos
this
a hacer este
ratio of the pull
ratio del tirón
eh of the jerks eh they
eh del tironas eh
will take out the comodi of the sentence
te van a sacar el comodi de la sentencia
without coming to the point and at all hours what
sin venir a cuento y a todas horas qué
money Of course but it's like what does it have to
plataa Claro pero es como qué tiene que
do with me insulting someone with what
ver que yo insulte a alguien con lo que
you defend maduro and apart from that you
tú defiendas a maduro y aparte tú me
are insulting me I sue you too
estás insultando te demando a ti también
and they put a fine on you Hey I also
y te ponen una murta Oye que también
have it I said it yesterday eh I told
tengo lo dije ayer eh se lo dije ayer a
another kid yesterday that let's see him now too
otro chaval que vamos a verlo ahora
that I also have a fine
también que también tengo una una multa
they gave me a fine 5 years ago because I was not wearing a
me pusieron una multa hace 5 años porque
seatbelt and and they took away three
iba sin cinturón y y me quitaron tres
points you can also put it there Wow
puntos podéis ponerlo también ahí Wow
Look they have taken away Three points
Mira te han quitado Tres puntos
W that complaint proves him right that it is not
W esa denuncia le da la razón que ni
even a complaint it is a lawsuit
siquiera es una denuncia es una demanda
a lawsuit is that someone asks you for money
una demanda es que alguien te pida pasta
but considers that you have done damage
pero considera que tú has hecho un daño
to his reputation let's
a su reputación
see that it is not firm you already know and I
a ver que no es firme ya lo sabéis y
trust that  It's going to change but
Confío en que eso va a cambiar pero
well, whether it changes or not, boy, look at the
bueno cambie o no cambie chico mírate la
story, look at yourself. Why did I react like this? I've
historia mírate Por qué reaccioné así
already said it. I mean, if
que yo ya lo he dicho O sea si de
suddenly someone comes and attacks me or
repente viene alguien y me ataca a mí o
my family or whatever, I don't rule out
a mi familia o lo que sea no descarto
that they could condemn me again at another
que me puedan volver a condenar en otro
time. It's about suing. I have
momento que la cosa Va de demandar yo
three people sued right now,
tengo demandado a tres ahora
okay Sara, but the
mismo vale Sara pero es que da igual la
sentence doesn't matter. This sentence is useless. This
sentencia esta sentencia no sirve esta
sentence doesn't discuss what I said, what I did
sentencia no discute lo que yo conté lo
n't say, whether it's true or a lie,
que no conté si es verdad o es mentira
it's just the expressions, to
son por las expresiones sin
be in a gang in El Salvador, you
más para estar en una banda del Salvador
must have sent a lobby that doesn't
debes de haber mandado lobby que no
share, you're so stupid, or they take us for fools,
compar tn tontos o nos toman de tontos a
no no, but anyway,
nosotros no no pero de todas maneras que
what am I saying here? I mean,
es lo que le estoy diciendo aquí o sea
the gang members in El
los pandilleros del
Salvador. Okay, and insulting someone, Ugh,
Salvador Vale y insultar a alguien Uf
how bad, I mean, he's just stupid, and
qué malo o sea es que es tonto y de
suddenly a lot of
repente me han aparecido muchos
little triangles and a lot of
triangulitos y muchas banderitas de
Palestinian flags and things like that appeared, you know, eh. And people
Palestina y cosas así sabes eh Y gente
like that, these types of accounts, and eh, it's
así de este tipo de cuentas y eh está
clear, I mean, eh, what he did was in
claro o sea eh lo que ha hecho es en
some group because it's almost instantly,
algún grupo porque es casi al instante
eh, post the tweet, boom  1000 like in some
eh poner el tweet pum 1000 lik en algún
group has been organized to put it yesterday
grupo se ha organizado para ponerlo ayer
something similar happened with another
pasó algo similar con otro
fool yesterday something similar happened with another
tonto ayer pasó algo similar con otro
fool who also defended maduro I mean they don't
tonto que también defendía a maduro o
fail they don't
sea es que no fallan no
fail they don't fail
fallan no fallan
eh the guy It
eh el tío
turns out that he was a turkey that we
Resulta ser que era un pavo que nosotros
had
habíamos
reacted we had reacted on
reaccionado habíamos reaccionado en
some occasion to one of his clicks because he
alguna ocasión a un click suyo porque se
messed with yuji in the past but look at
metió con yuji en el pasado pero fijaros
how the move is also look at how
como es la movida fijaros además el
macho he is eh
pedazo de machista que es eh
look the same since Fran threatened to
mira lo mismo desde que Fran me amenazó
report me a servant almost took his
con denunciarme un siervo casi le quita
life already be happy about this with this it would be
vida ya alegrarte de esto con esto
enough with this the T would be worth
valdría con esta el T ya valdría
okay And the thing is that I hadn't recognized him
vale Y es que yo no lo había reconocido
but it turns out that this guy was one of us
pero resulta de que este chico fue uno
reacted here to a video of his
que reaccionamos aquí a un vídeo suyo
because the guy messed with yuji to without
porque el tío se metió con yuji para sin
pear at Princessita I mean to mess with
pear a Princesita o sea para meterse con
Fran to hurt Fran he messed
Fran para hacerle daño a Fran se metió
with yuji then he apologized because he
con yuji luego pidió perdón porque se
realized that people were
dio cuenta que la gente se le echó
on him and then he did a live show that the
encima y luego hizo un directo que el
guy was pitiful Oh with that face
tío daba una penita Ay con la carita esa
there you know total han  sentenced to his
ahí sabes total han condenado a su
alleged current partner for spreading
presunta actual pareja por por difundir
the face and data of minors be I
la cara y los datos de menores sea yo
am Cristina and here I would have a lawsuit
soy Cristina y aquí tendría una demand
eh Because Cristina has not been convicted
eh Porque a Cristina no le han condenado
for spreading the face and data of
por difundir la cara y los datos de
anyone Cristina has been convicted because of
nadie a Cristina le han condenado porque
a tweet that she posted that I see the tweet
un twet que puso que yo lo veo el tweet
the truth is a [ __ ] I have not
la verdad una chorrada no he opinado
yet commented on that subject I am going to wait for it to be
todavía sobre ese tema voy a esperar que
confirmed I am saving it all okay
se afirme estoy guardándolo todo vale
But the T also cut in the sentence
Pero el T además cortado en la sentencia
and I do not see it at all, I mean he was
y yo no lo veo para nada o sea el era
literally narrating what the girls were saying
literalmente narrando lo que decían las
in a video that had gone
chicas en un vídeo que se había hecho
viral on Facebook okay in that video you could not
viral en Facebook vale en ese vídeo ni
see the face of any girl or of
se veía la cara de ninguna chica ni de
this girl who was reporting nor
esta chica que denunciaba ni vamos ni
any
ningún
information okay they have sentenced his friend javil
dato vale han condenado a su amigo javil
veira to a payment of 9000 his friend Dallas
veira a un pago de 9000 su amigo Dallas
in an alleged crypto scam they are going
en una presunta estafa de criptos le van
to throw him out of Thailand his own ex
a desar de Tailandia su propia ex
okay and I put it What a bad combination it is to
vale y le pongo Qué mala combinación es
be bad and stupid at the same time you know the one
ser malo y tonto a la vez sabes la de
that You are bad bad bad and on top of that you
que Eres malo malo malo y encima te
think you are smart well that is the case okay And what
crees listo pues es el caso vale Y que
was his response What was his
Cuál fue su respuesta Cuál fue su
response  I may be bad and stupid but I have not
respuesta seré malo y tonto pero a mí no
been sentenced to pay 9000 more in
me han condenado a pagar 9000 má costas
legal costs where Also a video is leaked of you
procesales donde Además se te filtra un
making a fool of yourself in front of
vídeo donde haces el ridículo frente a
an Andalusian lawyer
un abogado andaluz
and I don't make a fool of myself first of all it
e yo no hago ningún ridículo primero no
has nothing to do with what we are
tiene nada que ver con lo que estamos
discussing okay it is still bad and
discutiendo vale sigue siendo malo y
stupid You are bad and stupid although even if I
tonto Eres malo y tonto aunque aunque yo
insult someone and I am sentenced you are
insulte a alguien y me condenen tú eres
bad and stupid you understand me but now I
malo y tonto me entiendes pero ahora me
get into the profile tasty old man How
meto en el perfil viejo sabroso Cómo
are you My throat is already hurting a little
estás Ya me está doliendo un poco la
let's finish this topic and
garganta vamos a terminar este tema y
we go
nos vamos
to what was said Even if they sentence me
em lo dicho Aunque a mí me condenen
because even if I insult someone as
porque aunque yo insulte a alguien como
if now I curse the dead people on half of
si ahora me cago en los muerto de medio
Twitter and I am sentenced okay I will pay the
Twitter y me condenan vale yo pago la
fine But you are stupid and bad you are
multa Pero tú eres tonto y malo tú eres
stupid and bad okay the click that was
tonto y malo vale igual el click que se
leaked the click that was leaked is
filtró el click que se filtró es un
obviously the only one that they
click evidentemente es el único que les
could have liked from the trial or the one that they
pudo gustar del juicio o el que más le
liked the most okay And I said it when they leaked
gustó vale Y yo lo dije cuando filtraron
those two minutes that were leaked of course it was
esos dos minutos que se filtró claro lo
leaked by a journalist who coincidentally
filtró un periodista que casualmente
is also a client apart from being a good friend
también es cliente aparte de buen amigo
of the same lawyer  that these
del mismo abogado que esta
people are worth it because they got angry because I told him
gente vale porque se picó porque le dije
on Twitter, shocking The countryman because he
en Twitter chocal La paisano porque él
also Sanchez has a conviction for
también Sánchez tiene una condena por
insulting a
insultar a una
woman the same conviction he has 6000 for
mujer la misma condena tiene 6000 por
insulting a woman on Twitter
insultar a una mujer en Twitter
okay of course me when they leaked that video of
vale claro yo cuando filtraron ese vídeo
course Hey I'm delighted that you put the
claro Oye yo encantado de que pongáis el
video up I have no problem but I
vídeo no tengo ningún problema pero yo
want to put it up in its entirety in its entirety so that you can
lo quiero poner entero entero entero que
see their testimony and that
se vea la testifical de de ellas y las
of their witness Of course I
del testigo de ellas Claro a mí me
would love to but it can't be seen no no no
encantaría pero no se ve que no que
whole no whole no those two
entero no que entero no que esos dos
minutes are okay but What's he
minutitos vale pero A qué
responding to
responde
okay In the
vale
end what did I
Total qué le
tell him you piece of clown they haven't
dije pedazo de payaso no te han
convicted you because they haven't sued you
condenado porque no te han demandado
you have insults on your profile so
tienes insultos en tu perfil para que lo
a few can do it I get involved and he has a
hagan unos cuantos me meto y tiene a un
lot of people to whom he calls garbage
montón de gente a la que le dice basura
[ __ ] [ __ ] and that kind of thing what
[__] subnormal y ese tipo de cosas que
are the convictions are by right to
son las condenas está por derecho al
honor without going any further for without pear to
honor sin ir más lejos por sin pear a
Princess you messed with
Princesita te metiste con
Yuji for free and you called her a
yuji gratuitamente y la llamaste
drug dealer among other things What do you
narcotraficante entre otras cosas Qué te
think would have happened to you and take it and they
crees que te hubiera pasado y coge y
say that I called her a drug dealer  to a
dicen que llamé narcotraficante a una
person convicted of drug trafficking What
persona condenada por narcotráfico What
time now I support her more than ever
time ahora la apoyo más que nunca
[ __ ] you an
joderos una
outrage stupid stupid
barbaridad
very stupid I mean you mess with
tonto tonto muy tonto o sea te metes con
a woman and you slander her because she has not
una mujer y la calumnias porque ella no
been convicted of drug trafficking she was
ha sido condenada por narcotráfico salió
acquitted in the
libre de cargos en el
appeal okay Why do you speak to me in
recurso vale Por qué me hablas en
English second and third I mean he asked at the
inglés segundo y tercero o sea pidió en
time Forgiveness for having messed with
su momento Perdón por haberse metido con
Yuji for having messed up because he
yuji por haber metido la pata porque se
messed with Yuji to try to hurt
metió con yuji para intentar hacer daño
a man he was
a un hombre con el que se estaba
fighting with and now because I'm making him look
peleando y ahora porque lo estoy dejando
ridiculous he
yo en ridículo
messes with Yuji again So
vuelve a meterse con yuji Entonces por
why why did you apologize
qué por qué te disculpaste
because you're a sexist and You're only
porque eres un machista y Solamente eres
a you do the s to see if you get Cacho
un haces el s para ver si pillas Cacho
on
en
Twitter because you see him sympathizing with
Twitter porque te lo ves simpeando a
all the girls you're of the same
todas las chicas estas de la misma
string you're a simp You're a piece of
cuerda eres un simp Eres un pedazo de
simp you're not going to get laid because they
simp así no vas a [__] porque se dan
realize that you're a piece of sexist
cuenta de que eres un pedazo de machista
attack me don't attack a woman to
atácame a mí no ataques a una mujer para
try to discredit
intentar desacreditarme a
me okay well total a
mí vale bueno total un
clown people what what  what what topic do I put
payaso gente qué qué qué qué tema pongo
in the what topic do I have in the title Juan
en el qué tema tengo en el título Juan
Guarnizo responds
guarnizo responde
man but I have to go I'm going to
tío pero es que me tengo que ir voy a
change the title of the live and I'm going to
cambiar el título del directo y voy a
put it
ponerle
i and I'm going to put this one and tomorrow we continue okay my
iy a ponerle este y mañana seguimos vale
throat is getting a little swollen I'm going to take an anti-inflammatory
garganta me voy a tomar antinflamatorio
and I'm going and I'm
y me voy y me
going guys Tomorrow we'll see each other Thank you so much
voy chicos mañana nos vemos Muchísimas
for this little while okay tomorrow we'll see each other
gracias por este ratito vale mañana nos
more for sure I'm going to
vemos más más tiempo seguro voy a
try to see if in the morning I can record the news I'm going to
intentar a ver si por la mañana grabo
try to see if in
noticieros voy a intentar a ver si por
the morning I can record the news or something
la mañana grabo noticieros o algo
and and we'll give it a go to the three channels
y y le damos caña ya a los tres canales
damn Well, I saw the editor while I
[__] Pues el editor lo he visto yo que
was traveling around I don't know if I do
estaba por ahí de viaje no sé si
n't know if it's final what a kiss
no sé si es definitivo qué un beso
handsome I love you Thank you so much for this
guapos os quiero Muchísimas gracias por
little while tomorrow
el ratillo mañana
we talk What's up What's up read the chat
hablamos Qué pasa Qué pasa lee el chat
It's about the lady What's up What's up
Es sobre la señora Qué pasa Qué pasa
Ah we've already said it We've already said it we've said it we've said it we've talked about it we've talked about it we've talked about it
Ah ya lo hemos dicho Ya lo hemos
Ah [ __ ] you scared me I
hablado Ah [__] me habéis asustado me
thought there was some [ __ ] do
crea que había alguna [__] es que
you know what came to my
sabéis lo que se me ha venido a la
head I say  Can you imagine it's not and
cabeza digo te imaginas que no es y
we've messed up? Come on guys,
hemos metido la pata venga chicos que
rest up. Okay, tomorrow we'll try to get back to
descanséis vale mañana intentamos volver
full speed. And thanks for the
a darle caña a todo y gracias por el
little while. Kisses, guys.
ratito un beso guapos
[Music]
[Música]